People of the Internet.
Once again, we start a new game.
In Neuse.
Yes, my son, it is I, God himself.
Where am I merely a person conveying the message of the gods?
I'm sorry, I'm just having too much fun with that.
Oh, man, I gotta utilize that stuff more.
You can do so much crazy shit, you know?
I just love that stuff.
What's up, people?
So it has been written and so it has been spoken.
Creamy Mami, thank you for resubscribing.
What does that first part of your name mean?
Is that the same thing?
Creamy Mami, just in... I don't know what language that is.
I can't tell based on the characters.
You'd have to let me know.
Oliver, do you use a stream deck?
I do actually.
I do.
I bought it just for this stuff and it's super, super awesome.
I'm even using it for stuff outside of streaming too.
It's an incredible thing.
Like just muting myself on Discord or whatever the hell, you know?
You can do everything with that.
It's amazing.
It means the same?
Okay.
Who's ready to make Busted Ones?
I am.
Me, me, me.
I'm so excited.
And you know the best part?
Like, here's the thing.
People have said that insanity is doing the same thing and expecting different results.
But that's exactly what this game is.
You do the same thing every time.
But you get different results.
How awesome is that?
You get new perks.
You get new situations.
Everything's new.
Well, sort of.
And I love that.
It's fun.
Exactly.
You have 11,000 potatoes.
Sadahu, you gotta, you gotta gamble all those potatoes.
You should make some predictions.
If there are any mods today, they can make predictions.
Or something.
However, I was wondering, do you listen to the song Not Like Us by Kendrick Lamar?
Uh, yeah.
I have heard it.
Yeah.
It's okay.
I like it.
But what I really like is Eminem's new album.
Oh yeah.
I've been missing the old Eminem.
I've been fucking eating that up so good.
I think I'm just gonna jump right in, guys.
I'm too excited.
I gotta play this game.
I gotta fill out my map.
I gotta explore more things.
I gotta build more ones.
I need to know it.
You know how it is.
The addiction is real.
It's there.
I'm closing you guys down.
Thank you for joining the stream and checking it out.
I appreciate it.
It's super cool having you guys here.
Okay.
New game.
I'm actually kind of confused why it says new game.
Didn't I start a new run?
Like and then quickly exit?
Or did I just I guess I just clicked exit last time.
But whatever.
We died at the very end last time.
So we are starting fresh.
And you know how I always mention how slow I will be doing things?
Today is for real.
I'm really gonna play slow.
Don't believe me?
Watch.
Oh, what do we have here?
Look at that Hamus group over there.
That's a lot of Hamuses.
Holy shit.
And they were all stacked on each other too.
I gotta get that money before it disappears.
That's a lot of money right there.
Do I have toxic?
Guys, I will call this poison.
I don't care.
To me, green is poison.
Okay.
Doesn't matter what it is.
Purple, green.
I'm colorblind.
It's the same thing.
Let me fill up the water bottle.
Oh no.
Oh, okay.
Perfect.
Now I see more Hamuses.
We are in the hemisphere after all.
This is their habitat.
And they need to be dealt with.
I am on their home turf, so...
It's not... Oh, that thing is gonna explode.
Oh, I have an idea.
Yes, sir.
Beautiful.
Oh, there's a chest right there.
Holy shit.
Wow.
There's spells in there.
What the hell?
Have I ever seen that?
I don't know if I have.
Weird.
Okay, cool.
Now I wonder what else can be in those chests.
Like, that's what I mean.
I feel like I've never seen that before and now suddenly the game is like, you know what?
Here, have a couple of spells.
Like, what?
That's dope.
Okay, I'm watered.
That's good.
Let me have a shotgun, man.
I shouldn't be diving after that gold like that.
It's a bit risky.
Let's keep an eye out.
Ehuerta?
Perfect.
Can't get through there.
I see a wand below me.
Very cool.
But first, let me just fill out this area here and turn this into water.
Ah, you know what?
I'll go for the wand immediately.
Whoops.
Don't even think about it, sir.
Oh no, we've got... Is that whiskey?
It sure is.
It's raining whiskey.
Some people pay good money for that sort of thing.
Not me though.
Yeah, I'll take that.
That's dope.
I don't like that fire.
I'm not going that way.
Nope.
I could water myself, but nah.
Not this time.
I have a good feeling about this run, guys.
This is the one.
This is the one where I become all powerful and I slay all the enemies and all the bosses and I discover the most valuable of secrets.
Can you feel it?
I feel it.
So far, so good.
Although, I would have preferred to have a heart in that chest now that I think about it.
Fuck those spells.
Unless those spells were amazing, of course.
It's all relative.
Let's see what we got here.
Yo!
That's pretty sick.
That's a decent wand for killing hemasus in the hemisphere.
Look at that inverted pyramid.
Isn't that striking?
Kind of looks like the mountain on top of the starting area with the snow pile on top.
It's except here.
It's reversed and it's green coal.
Very weird.
In fact, I'm going to put this here.
This is now my main wand.
Oh, do we have maybe a heart down there?
Don't shoot me.
Did I actually kill him?
No way.
Wow.
The damage is legit, man.
Ah, there's always something below this sort of water container.
Have you noticed?
I bet if you play this game enough, you will start to recognize commonalities and you sort of know where to go and explore.
I will use my fireball because that can dig, right?
Wait, can it dig?
I'm not sure.
No, it cannot dig.
Shit.
Okay.
That was wrong.
We put a bomb here.
I want... Ooh.
Hello.
That's not bad either.
That's pretty much a better version of this.
And with light, guys.
Guys.
We get to... Oh, wow.
This is great.
We get to go in the cave.
We can totally cave it.
Oh, I thought a fire dude was coming down, but it's actually just a beam on fire.
Toxic rock.
Now, how do I... Okay.
I'm, I'm, I'm watered up.
I should be fine here.
Yep.
Lovely.
My ears itchy.
Let's go this way.
Hello.
Dude, this one is sick.
Like you just spam that shit.
Things, things die.
Like in this first level here.
Pretty dope.
Thank you.
Having a nice bath in the toxic sludge.
I can respect it.
Let's go take him out though.
Excuse me, Huerta.
I shall convert it to water.
Mix it up good.
I'm calling it now, by the way.
This is the run.
Collapsed mines.
Uh, I can get through here with this, I believe.
I can burn this.
Yep.
And I can... Oh, dude, I can also go here.
Of course.
I'm gonna come down here.
Nice.
I'm also gonna open up here.
Just because.
This is patient gameplay right here and it's paying off so far.
It really is.
I'm gonna try and make this the best hemisphere ever.
I see you down there.
Where did you go?
There you are.
Oh man, it's so good.
Wow.
Why is it so good?
Come on.
How much does this do?
Five damage per, but I feel like it's way more.
That's crazy.
I guess it does shoot four at the same time, but I feel like I just hit that guy only once with one of them.
But I guess I was wrong.
Not complaining though.
Love it.
We can open up here.
You know, maybe I've been sleeping on the bubble spark.
I think I should try and make a cool wand out of that.
I mean, they are kind of nice, you know, and if you get speed up and you can, you know, modify it a little bit, make it super cool.
Like, look at that.
It's just gonna bounce around in there and kill whatever it hits.
There it is.
He's dead.
Fantastic.
Wait, is this digging?
Holy shit!
But only when they explode, have you noticed?
So they explode after a while.
Oh, is that what's doing the extra damage?
They sort of pop after a short time and then they dig with that pop.
I could technically go on top of the mountain with this and get the health.
Yeah, yep, yep.
I also light things up.
Oh, that's actually sweet.
Just do this before I go in.
Get a view of what's going on.
Getting rid of all the explosives.
Oh, yeah.
Dead end.
Oh, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo.
Be careful here.
Running a little low on water.
Okay, so these are the roots of the tree.
That means I'm close.
Oh, what was that?
That was a frog.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, don't destroy the potion.
Or maybe, hmm.
Worm pheromone.
Yo, I just discovered maybe a way to efficiently kill worms.
I hatch a worm.
No, I make a pool of worm pheromone.
And then it'll go to that, right?
Because it's pheromone.
And then I can easily kill it.
It's like a lure.
I'm gonna try that at some point.
Oh, hold on.
Throw this down there.
And I guess I can explode this as well.
Yep, that's fine.
That is fine.
Blow that wide open.
Oh, that's very fiery.
I do need to drain this before I can go in, because I cannot hold my breath.
But I can do that.
I have two bombs left.
If I open here and there, it's gonna go like this down that way.
This one I can open with my... I believe.
Well, if I do it from up here, maybe.
Yeah, sort of, sort of.
Not bad.
Not bad at all.
Whoops.
I just need them to pop right next to that little piece there.
There we go.
Look at that.
Lovely.
Then I use a bomb here.
Let the water flow.
Oh, it's gonna flow this way.
Oh, that works.
It's gonna go that way.
And then I need another bomb down here.
Maybe right there.
Sweet.
Dig it.
Nice.
So that's gonna drain, and now we have light.
So I'm gonna go up top now.
The advanced strategies are coming out here.
Do I even have a way up there?
That is the question.
Maybe if I have... maybe I have to get rid of this.
Look at that.
Oh, but wait, there's a tree in the way.
Shit.
Maybe I don't have an access in there.
That's very unfortunate.
I maybe have to do it from below.
Yeah.
Let's see if we can't do it from below.
We have light.
Also, I should pick up more water here.
Let's grab some of this.
Okay.
You know, technically you could go in there with an empty bottle and just step by step empty the entire cave of water.
It sounds insane.
It's like getting rid of water in your boat with a bucket.
But it works kind of.
Okay, so we need more water to drain here, for sure.
We should make a hole here.
Oh, that's gonna take a while, I think.
Problem is they bounce off and they go up here and pop there.
So maybe if I go at a distance...
So they slow down over there.
No, that's not gonna work.
Hmm.
I mean, maybe... Oh, oh, you see that?
Hey, hey, look at that, look at that.
Can I make that swim?
Last time I died in here trying to do this.
I can get some air here.
I can probably dig this.
I'm not drowning.
I'm digging.
I'm not digging anything, nevermind.
So there's a little spot here I can probably get in.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, definitely, definitely.
Oh yeah, look at that.
Okay, we're out of mana.
Wait, the audio is sort of bugging.
Oh, it's because I'm shooting on the water maybe.
How do I get it to dig up here?
Almost.
Nah, I don't think it's gonna work, guys.
I'm gonna explore some more.
Maybe I'll find some explosive.
If I can find a single TNT, that's pretty much it.
That's all we need.
And I haven't even explored the right side of this place.
So let's just go do that.
I was trying to see if I could make it work with what I had, but I think I can give it enough time.
I just don't want to spend forever.
That's basically it.
Like here, haven't explored this part yet.
I hate these lamps, man.
They said fire to everything.
Actually, now I need it.
So burn it.
You can burn that and I'm gonna go around while that burns.
That's the old wand.
Right, this is the spot.
Oh, toxic rock.
Oh, why is that all toxic?
I wonder.
That does not look good at all.
I wonder if there's a heart down there or something.
Wait, I can see that with my light.
Hold on a second.
And this bounces around.
Reveal.
Oh, I don't see anything.
Isn't this cool?
It's like a flashlight in a way.
Bouncing flashlight projectiles.
I think I should start having light on all of my spells.
Like on my damage wand when I have room for it.
Just put some light on it.
It can only be good for you.
There's no downside to it.
I think except mana caused of one, which is pretty okay.
If we convert this from up here, water's gonna drip down and it's gonna convert the rest.
Strategy.
Whoops.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay, it looked like he was still alive for a second there.
Scared me.
Give me that gold.
Thank you.
Now we're gonna take a look what's down here.
It's hard to say.
Nothing.
Okay.
I guess I'm going around.
Oh, I'm old up.
That's bad.
Damn it, dead end.
Chaotic polymorphine.
Yeah, I don't know about that one, man.
I wonder if you can turn yourself into a boss.
Like, imagine.
And then just kill everything while you're polymorphed.
You can apparently turn yourself into all kinds of enemies, right?
So maybe that's also an option.
This is the edge.
That means we can get our tablet too.
A deadly weapon in the right hands.
A.K.A.
not my hands.
Someone else's.
Let's get rid of that coal.
Let's get it.
I think I'm gonna have a dedicated keybind to this thing.
Maybe R.
Okay.
R is my tablet keybind.
I guess I could put it here, which is T for me.
T would make sense for tablet.
Let's use T.
Yeah, that makes more sense.
Hold on.
Hold up, hold up, hold up.
There's a little area there.
Look at that.
It's gonna burn down here at some point and reveal what's inside of there.
I'm okay with that.
Just the other side of the toxic place.
Did I actually explore all of this now?
No way.
Okay, so I'm gonna go up top now and grab the extra HP on the mountain.
I can do it.
I have what it takes.
I guess I could bring an explosive to the cave as well.
It's gonna be a bit too annoying to bring this all the way there, but maybe there's an explosive close by.
There's a dark area here.
What is down here?
The hammers.
Blow it.
All right, nothing else here.
We got the money though.
700 buckaroos.
That's not bad.
700 buckies in our pocket.
That's a good day.
Oh, we can get up there.
Watch.
Can we burn through this?
Water's gonna drain and everything's fine.
Oh no, it's not gonna drain all the way.
Uh, oh, that's electrified.
That's real bad.
Give me some water.
Okay, I thought I explored all of the hemisphere.
I guess I didn't.
What is going on here?
Why is this hanging here?
Amos?
Is there anything in here?
No.
What happens now?
It's gonna electrocute the water.
Yeah.
Yeah, just destroy it, I guess.
Hmm.
I'm very curious about that.
It's kind of odd that it's like hanging there like that.
Like, almost feels like a puzzle of some sort.
Oh, Huerta, I have a present for you.
Look, watch.
Oh, I would have been cool if that hit him in the face.
Instead, I have a tablet.
Boink.
My guy.
Die.
Jesus.
Okay, I'm gonna... I actually fucked up here.
I need to grab that tablet.
Water myself?
This is a new practice I've started doing.
Whenever there's fire, it protects me.
Pretty smart, I would say.
Dude, this wand is carrying me in this place right now.
I mean, not that this place is hard.
I haven't even discovered any of the fire dudes yet.
But it's like, really good.
It's super comfortable to kill people with.
Like, when you're out there killing people, comfort is one of the main things, you know, you need to worry about.
Can you do it comfortably or not?
Look how careful I'm being.
Incredible.
Maybe there is a way for us to get to the cave from the top.
Not that it matters anymore, but I just feel like we may be close to that.
What's up, hymns?
How's your day?
Mine is great.
Lovely Sunday.
Nothing here either, huh?
Oh, that's gonna burn through.
That's nice.
I do enjoy that.
Nothing up there.
I don't see anything.
Man, severe lack of hearts here.
What the hell?
Show me the love, man.
Got some more water here.
There's also stuff here and there.
Wow.
Okay, so here's an explosive.
Let's not destroy that yet, just in case we may need it.
That lamp is off.
Hold on, can I turn them off?
Huh.
How is that lamp off?
Isn't that interesting?
So there's something in here.
Can't get to it, unfortunately, but I can also send my little thing in to see what's going on over there.
Not much.
I am gonna go, though.
Put the dye in the process.
Okay, let's set up.
It's time to grab the HP.
Hopefully, I can do it comfortably with the bubble spark and it's not gonna be awkward.
It's probably gonna be awkward, right?
Because I'm gonna have to fly up there and... Oh, no.
Yeah, I'm not sure.
Oh, wait, where can I get through here?
I have no more bombs.
I actually have nothing left.
Oh, whoa, I did not see that explosive.
I did not see that at all.
Holy shit.
All I saw was him and my mind went kill.
So I did.
Goddamn.
Hold on.
Let me in.
Ah, this is gonna... Nah, I won't be able to dig with this.
It's gonna be torture.
I'm not doing it.
We need something more substantial, like a TNT.
Now, if only I could find one of those...
return ones right now.
I could jump through the portal, hopefully find a nice spell, and then get the fuck out again.
But I think we're pretty much done exploring here.
Let's go to a portal.
Let's just go.
I can't find anything else here.
We're done.
I could give it a last try in the cave with the bubble spark.
Yeah, you know, I'm gonna do it.
I worked so hard for that.
I'm gonna try one last time.
Like, I was... I needed like two centimeters of digging, right?
Like nothing.
Oh, and water's still draining, actually.
So I may have a shot.
I know what's happened here since.
It's pretty much at the same spot.
Come on, dig.
Dig for me.
Okay, I think we're sort of doing it.
I'm digging down somehow.
Oh, yes, it's happening.
It's happening.
We got it.
Ta-da!
I have made it.
Very cool.
We did it.
Yes, sir!
Mission successful, baby.
Now we go.
Oh, I'm so happy about that.
Okay.
We heal up.
And we look.
What is in the shop?
The luminous drill.
Sea of flammable gas.
Uh, what's this?
Sea of water.
Huh.
That could be cool.
Then we have kills to mana.
Faster wands.
And this was... I hate this thing.
Why would anyone take that?
Re-roll.
Boomerang spells.
Repelling cape.
That could be not bad.
Trick greed.
I feel like re-rolling again.
But let me buy some of the stuff I need first.
That is nice.
Uh, we already have a double.
We could go for this one.
It's also 50% off.
Just in case we find infinite spells later on, because that would be insanity.
I think I want sea of water.
Isn't that crazy?
Plus this one.
That leaves me with 402 golds.
So I can do another re-roll.
Yeah, let's do it.
Nice.
And then we re-roll once more.
What's that?
Wand radar?
Close call?
Faster movement.
Hmm.
I think I may want this.
As long as there are enemies near me.
Which is all the time, right?
So I think that's actually a solid one.
Okay.
Now.
This wand has 190 mana max, which is not bad.
And 52 mana charge speed.
It is shuffle.
So that's a bit of a bummer.
But look at the castelay.
It's so low.
Slow fiery bolts.
Recharge time is also kind of low on that.
This one is lower though.
Yo, that's sick!
Although the mana charge speed is atrocious.
So not very good, actually.
Could go nuts with the bouncing burst.
Let's see how good this is.
This is a solid spell.
Like 25 damage is pretty damn good.
Right?
But then again, the wand in itself was actually pretty damn good as well with the bubble spark.
So maybe I have both wands for one situation and another situation.
See, this wand is great for that.
That's perfect, honestly.
Yeah.
This is gonna be my chain bolt wand, and then we're gonna have a bubble spark wand.
We also gotta use our luminous drill, of course.
Or it's a good place to use that.
This is shuffle, 0.23, 0.47.
Maybe it's actually better to do this.
Okay, that's not as good.
Oh, it loosens mana quick, though.
Luminous drill, huh?
Is it worth it to get it, though?
That's what I'm wondering.
So hold on, fire bolt?
Fire bomb.
I think that dicks as well.
I'm not entirely sure.
That seems like a good, like, wand as well to have.
We can put some light in here.
It's shuffle, but it's gonna put it in at some point.
It's not bad.
Might as well have some light.
And maybe I put sea of water in one of them.
I mean, okay, here's the thing.
With the drill, we could technically leave the holy mountain without collapsing it.
Ah, but we're gonna make Zed angry.
So...
Can I kill him?
Dude, honestly, maybe the chain bolt is able to penetrate a shield.
It penetrates walls, right?
Maybe this is the one.
Like I said last time, I need to figure out a way to consistently deal with this dude.
So...
Right?
Oh, I could also try.
Oh, dude, I just had a genius idea.
Let's say I find...
Dude, you could be so creative.
Let's say I found an Ukuskivi.
Right?
I could use sea of water here, make a big bath, and then just electrify the water.
Put an Ukuskivi down there and pull the guy to me.
He's gonna walk through the water because the water level is gonna be up to here.
And hopefully he would die from that.
I mean, that's a way of doing it.
Right?
The only question is, how do I get through it myself then?
That's a bit of an issue.
But that is technically possible, I guess.
You could do it.
I do think I want to try and...
Yeah, I'm gonna fight Zed.
I'm fighting him.
I'm probably gonna die here, but that's okay.
We gotta get through the fear.
And maybe this spell is enough to deal with him.
Although he does have a lot of HP, I think.
So, yeah.
Rip.
I'm gonna try and make him angry here.
And set up a trap somehow.
Oh wait, I still haven't tried my tablet.
I think I missed with that one last time.
So that's also an option.
You know what?
Let's try that.
And if the tablet fails, we're gonna shift over to the chain bolt.
Just to try both.
Okay.
All right, you mad bro?
Look how I'm vandalizing your temple.
You hate this.
You hate to see it.
Sir?
Come on.
Why are you not angry?
I need to put this somewhere else.
Oh, that's useless.
Uh...
Why is... sir?
Are you okay?
You know what?
I'm gonna make my bunker here then.
I want to try something.
If he's not gonna be angry, that's fine with me.
I'm pretty sure he's gonna be angry at some point though.
This is for future runs as well.
We are experimenting right now.
Uh... How is this one doing up here by the way?
Oh yeah, that's actually not bad.
And then we switch it around hot swap.
And one is low on mana.
This is so dumb.
We're doing it for science.
I can slowly enter now.
I'm kind of stuck here though.
So if he appears now, I'm fucked.
Okay, there we go.
Make a sweet tunnel here.
Why is he not angry yet?
Dude, I have an idea.
Oh, dude.
Watch this.
I hide away in here and I use this spell.
Wait.
I can shoot through it.
But can he hit me?
Huh?
Hey!
I'm my little bunker.
We're gonna try that for sure.
This is gonna be sick.
I actually have a really good feeling about this.
Let's switch these back.
Nice, put it back.
This is very scuffed, I understand.
Why is he not angry yet though?
If I can make it a little, if I can make the floor lower, I can also shoot down when he comes.
I don't want to make the opening too big though.
So hold on.
Uh, like that.
So when he comes, I can go...
Uh...
So I can't shoot right here.
Huh?
There it works.
You see?
Hell yeah.
Now the only, this all relies on the fact or on the hope that chain bolt will actually damage him and not just be absorbed by his shitty shield.
You know?
Maybe I have to make him angry in some other way.
Hold on, let me just keep digging.
At some point he got angry, right?
When I did this last time, I'm pretty sure.
Or did I dig up?
I don't remember.
Definitely if you dig up, it's gonna react at some point.
Put it here.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Here comes, here comes, here comes, here comes.
Set!
Come here!
Come here, set!
While he's doing that, I'm gonna be digging a little bit.
Make him angry.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, dude, that's fine.
Do your thing.
I'm gonna dig to here so there's a little room.
Oh man, I hate being low on mana.
This is actually painful.
Oh, this is not gonna work, is it?
Oh, not quite.
Recharge, come on.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Is he coming?
Oh, here we go, here we go, here we go.
Oh, he doesn't know where he is!
Bro, he's dumb as hell!
He's dumb!
Hey!
Set?
Big set?
Come on!
Come here, that's right!
Come here!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, where is he?
Where am I?
You don't know.
Oh shit, man.
What is this guy doing?
Come on.
Okay, while he's doing that, I'm gonna keep digging.
Don't even give a fuck.
Switch it.
My dude, come on!
Show thyself.
But guys, I think I've found a way to deal with him.
I just need to optimize this strategy so I can shoot him from here, you know?
Whoops, I'm stuck now.
Uh-oh.
Oh, there we go, there we go.
Let's be a little careful here.
Oh, he's coming fast!
Hey, sir!
Oh, he's angry!
He can't take it!
Reload, mana, mana, mana, mana, mana!
Oh, sick!
I did it!
I fucking did it!
Is that...
Hold on, there's something on the floor.
What is that on the floor there?
Okay, I'm not sure.
That is awesome!
That is fantastic.
Now we make our wands again.
Actually, I do gotta dig a little bit still, so we need to make a hole over here, of course.
Oh, dude, that was so good!
Absolutely lovely.
I love that.
Now what you guys gotta remember, don't go up here.
Very important.
Don't go up there.
That'll be dumb right now.
Oh, hello, sir.
Just get some mana.
Oh, yeah.
So when I find a luminous drill, I know that option is there.
So from now on, I'm always going to grab the tablet before I come here.
That's going to be one of the new rules.
But if I can't dig, then there's another issue, right?
Then I have to find some other way of doing it, of course.
Come on, recharge.
This takes forever!
But you know what?
If I have a teleport wand, I could make a small sliver in here and then just teleport through, you know?
So if I have that, I can at least make this a little bit easier on myself.
That's nice to know for the future.
This should be okay, right?
Yeah.
There we go.
There we fucking go, man!
Holy shit!
I'm so glad!
Incredible!
It smells like soil after rain.
And you know what?
I don't care.
I don't.
Is that going to become a thingy?
Maybe not.
But let's do this.
We are so back.
Hold on, I'm going to use my...
Shit, I forgot to change my wand.
But the thing is, we can go back and do that now.
That is such a good thing to do.
Wow.
I'll be killing all the sets.
Set's dead, baby!
Set's dead.
It's a rule for now that I have to say that when he's dead.
Uh, there we go.
Sure.
Very cool.
Now I have that.
And I also have the fire wand.
Does that dig, then?
Let's just double check.
It sets things on fire.
It does act- Okay, so this is coal.
It does dig!
Some, I think.
So on Grey Rock, not entirely sure.
Maybe it does, but very little amounts.
It's not fantastic or anything.
And we're still playing ultra safe.
What's over here?
I can get through there.
Ooh.
Very nice.
Let me, uh, open that, huh?
Holy shit!
Glowing lands!
This is my birthday.
Uh...
Replace that one for now.
And there's a lot of them too.
I'm going straight back.
Straight back to the lab.
Back to the lab again.
Oh, there goes gravity.
Let me see.
With a burning trail as well.
I don't like that.
I don't want to burn things.
By the way, I could have measured how much HP said had just before.
This one is actually not bad.
This is a decent want.
0.03.
Oh, this one is actually better.
I think if we just do this, this is straight up fantastic.
Like that is solid right there.
That is not bad.
Is that really 0.03?
Oh, no, wait.
It's adding cast delay.
Oh, right.
Hold on.
So maybe it's not worth it to get that many on here.
Let's see.
Wait, what?
Wait, why is that?
That is definitely using recharge time now.
Now it's not weird.
Or it is, but I only have two shots.
Huh.
That's interesting.
It adds 0.33 cast delay.
All right.
I mean, sure.
This is 0.03 cast delay.
How does that do?
Let's just try it.
Also pretty good.
I mean, it's nice.
And there's a lot of slots in this one.
May as well put all of these in here.
Why not?
And leave one of them up here.
Just in case we need it for later.
But I guess I can always come back here and change it.
Oh, you know what's so cool about this?
We will always have a spot now in this run where we can change our wants.
It's so big.
Unbelievable.
Fantastic.
35 damage on that.
That is fantastic.
I will put this one back up here, I think.
Yeah, that's fine.
No, keep the light up here.
Yeah.
What does this look like?
It looks exactly what you would expect.
Gotcha.
Why not?
Let's go.
It's gonna be my main want.
My main want.
Oh, yeah, baby.
Oh, I hate these things.
They just blocked my path and they set fire to everything.
It's horrible.
I'm just going back where I was.
Also, why is my want watery?
You see that?
It's like dripping water.
Am I crazy?
Weird.
My want is wet.
Yeah, go back over here.
Oh, hold on.
If you're like really close to them, you crit quite often with this perk.
It's really nice.
Yeah, get rid of this crap.
They drip poison as well.
Poison and fire is just two of the worst things.
So this is where we left that want, right?
Do I still want that want?
I mean, yeah, I think I do.
It is nice for digging.
This one is...
Maybe I'll just replace this.
I mean, optimally, I would go back and just put the fire bomb.
Yeah, I'm just going to move on with this.
This is fine.
I can come back for those bubble sparks if I actually want to use them.
It's so hard to hit with this without the speed on it.
What's that?
Volcanic rock.
And another wand.
What could it be?
Oh, I thought he had a cape on.
It was a flower.
Oh, oh, those flowers are going to fuck me.
Okay, not bad.
That's a lot of gold.
See, that's what I'm talking about.
That's digging right there.
Slow charge, though.
We water ourselves.
Go.
How do I get to that?
Oh, it's right here.
Ah, that's annoying.
You know, the chain bolt might actually be better.
Like for this part of the game, because there's such a huge distance between me and the enemies that it's hard to hit them when there's so much drop off on it.
It's actually the superior weapon here, I think.
I'm going to make a tunnel through there.
I may just use that as my main one right now.
What do we got?
Halle-fucking-lujah!
Holy shit, guys!
That's what I'm talking about!
We've got all the essentials here.
Damn!
Absolutely amazing.
I'm going straight back to the lab with that one.
Oh, I kind of want to clear this.
This is annoying.
That's fine.
Let's go.
Where's the exit?
Is it left or right?
I think it's left.
Sometimes I mistake the fire pixels for lava.
This is going to make life so much easier later.
We even have missiles that do 50...
That's actually a lot of damage.
Dude, we are so set.
It's insane.
Magic bolt.
Hold up, hold up, hold up.
Put all these there.
This one is obviously our new digger.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, it's so good.
Oh, lovely.
Okay, but I want to put it on a shuffle wand, I guess.
Because like this one.
380 mana max.
That's just a long recharge.
That's annoying, right?
The only thing.
Bubbly bounce makes projectiles shoot bubble sparks as it bounces.
Wouldn't that be kind of cool with the bubble sparks that I had?
Bounces plus one and it spawns more of them?
Not bad, right?
I think that sounds pretty dope.
Put that there.
We even have another rock if we need it.
Why is there a little circle on it?
Is he the golden circle on that?
I've noticed that.
What the fuck does that even mean?
No clue.
Hold on.
That's solid.
I like it.
0.22, 0.38.
I do like the magic bolt.
The magic bolt is pretty neat.
Oh, that's too slow.
So, like, it's one thing to look at the numbers.
It's another thing to just try it.
What's with the...
Oh, the spread on this is absolutely horrendous.
31 degrees of inherent spread.
Damn.
That's really bad.
See how good this one is.
Too slow.
Oh, that's definitely the one.
That is the one we're using.
However, this actually reduces recharge time.
Look at that.
It actually makes it faster.
Oh, yeah!
Pretty...
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh, cool!
Oh, it's with a timer.
It's getting shot at the end of where the luminous drills ends.
That's funny.
Very cool.
But I do run out of mana quick, and I do not enjoy that very much.
Maybe we can put this here.
I mean, it does have...
I mean, it's...
Yeah, look at the angle.
The angle is bad.
We don't want to be angling this accidentally wrong, you know?
You want to be precise with that one.
Bubbly...
I'm going to keep this one as well.
Also with that one.
So the vertical barrier.
A thin vertical barrier that harms passing creatures, including you.
You know, I'm going to have an open mind today.
I'm going to try to use this offensively and really try not to go through it.
Yeah.
That's very important.
And what I could do is do this to make it safe.
So I shoot like this.
Quite far away from it.
But if I don't do that, how close is it?
Okay, that's not bad, actually.
Maybe I'll use that instead.
And if enemies pass through, they take damage, huh?
How much damage, I wonder?
That is interesting.
Although it does kind of...
The effect of it does kind of remind me a bit of the plasma cutter.
Oh, not quite.
Like a slower version over a larger area.
Maybe it's the same idea where if you're standing, you continuously take damage.
That's what I think.
Now the bomb here, I don't think I'll use anymore.
It's empty and it's sad.
Nobody wants it.
It sounds harsh, but that is the truth.
Lightning bolt could be nice to have, but I am deathly afraid of lightning.
But it could be a nice, oh, someone needs to die right now, spell.
And then a missile.
This is my digger.
This goes here.
And we have the shield.
And this, I don't even know what I should put on this.
Maybe I will put something like that on.
Let's see here.
Let's just make sure we don't kill ourselves.
Okay, I like this setup.
I like this setup.
Let's go.
Also, quickly take a look at the spells we have back here.
Maybe we can combine something.
You know what?
I will be open-minded.
So I'm going to purchase the sea of flammable gas as well.
Dude, sea of flammable gas with burning trail.
Maybe you can make something cool with that.
Let's leave some of these here.
Bouncing bursts.
Although it could be cool to try and try these at some point for something.
So you know what?
I'm going to leave one rock because I'm never going to use both rocks.
If anything, I'm going to use one of these spells when I have unlimited spells.
And then I'm going to put a light here as well.
Costs one mana.
Yeah, that sounds good.
And maybe I can put a modifier on something.
This is 20 mana drain.
That's a static projectile.
Is that going to do what I think?
Hold on.
Oh, when it bounces.
This one is not bouncing anywhere.
Right.
Okay, that makes sense.
All right.
I do kind of like this.
I feel more safe with this, guys.
Like, I'm deadly afraid of the vertical barrier.
So having more distance...
Like, I couldn't see myself accidentally jumping, making it and jumping through it, you know?
So I'm playing it safe here.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Also, I forgot to buy the Sea of Flammable Gas.
Whatever.
I'll buy this later.
Okay.
Let's move on.
So now I have this spell, which is my main damage thing.
And it does 13 damage per shot.
Hey, nice.
Some more health.
And then we have the lightning bolt.
I am actually...
Maybe I should have used the chain bolt here instead of lightning bolt.
I'm quickly gonna go back, guys.
I need the optimal setup here.
I feel like I would kill myself with the lightning bolt.
I'm playing it safe.
Although I am pretty good with it.
Like, I've used it a bunch of times.
I'm quite proficient with the lightning bolt.
But we are kind of low on HP, right?
So let's just take the necessary precautions here.
I'm gonna put this in here.
And then I'm also gonna take this one since I'm here anyway.
Formation...
I don't care about that, I don't think.
I'll take another one of those.
And then we move.
That's the setup.
So I'm imagining with this one here, the vertical barrier, I'm gonna kite someone somewhere.
You know?
And when they follow me, they walk through it.
Oh my god.
Fuck yeah.
It's looking great.
Wait, hold on.
Is this very inaccurate?
Oh, it is kind of inaccurate.
Guys, it's very high spread on that.
Don't like that.
That's hard to hit with.
Good thing we have this.
Does this dig?
Oh yeah, does dig!
That's big.
I could make a shortcut up here now.
If I wanted to.
Oh man, all that lava.
Out of water.
I'm getting some.
This is me playing the most safe and optimal way I can imagine.
And that does...
I don't mean going places I haven't been.
I mean going this way.
Almost went the wrong way there.
We know there's water here, so we take it.
In fact, I will fill two bottles of water.
I don't think I care about the worm pheromone.
Let's put this in a pile somewhere and maybe a worm will come.
Let's convert this.
Where did that guy come from?
In fact, just put it here.
It's gonna fall to the bottom.
There we go.
Away it goes.
This is another experiment.
Maybe the worms will come here now.
Okay.
Can we grab more water?
And what about the polymorphine that we have here?
Let's keep it.
Who knows?
So I can get down here now.
God, I've missed this plasma cutter.
Such a good fucking spell.
I gotta be honest here.
I find myself using the chain bolt the most out of all these.
It's just so good.
Don't catch fire.
Get rid of that plant.
Back to the arboretum you go.
Or wherever the fuck it is you came from.
Flow down hill.
I will grab that.
Like if there's easy gold like that, I'm taking it.
Let's fill up the water bottle.
I have to remember, I also have my tablet for emergencies.
What's happening here?
Why is this wood so suspicious looking?
Something's going on here.
Or not.
Wait, what?
Is there something in here?
Hmm, that felt like a puzzle almost.
I guess it wasn't.
Oh, almost walked into it.
Maybe this is not the most optimal way to go, but fuck it.
It works.
Whoop!
That was a bit scary.
Oh, that's so good.
It went through all of them.
Come here.
Okay, we got to take care of that nest.
Like look how inaccurate this is.
I'm holding the cursor in the same spot and yet it still sort of shoots it everywhere.
I don't think I have that much gold.
Yeah, this is my long distance wand.
Even though it's kind of shit at long distance.
Better than my A-chain bolt.
Doesn't go very long.
Wait, that just disintegrates it.
Yeah, you don't want to be using that for this.
Do not use the plasma cutter on the gold.
Wow!
Oh my god, come on.
There we go.
Ow!
Little asshole.
Okay, let's just wait for that shit to go away.
Blow it!
Sweet.
Everything dies and that makes me happy.
Oh, hello, sir.
I see you in there.
How fuck you?
Oh, oh no.
No, not this place.
Anything but this place.
Oh no.
How much HP do you have, man?
Gimme.
All right, I'm gonna chill here while I wait.
This is getting very tricky.
Oh, okay, twitchy finger gone.
Good.
What is this?
What?
What do you mean silver?
I gotta try that immediately.
Uh, chaotic.
Let's gently put this down.
Silver?
What?
Huh.
It's just silver.
He went away.
I'm in a bad spot, guys.
I don't want to be in here.
I need to leave immediately.
Yep.
Good thing I was at the border here.
Ah, you motherfucker!
From off screen.
I hate you.
Man, I lost almost all my HP.
That right there...
is annoying.
So I gotta find my way out now.
I gotta get out.
Gimme this.
Also, gimme that one.
Like right there.
Thank you.
All right, let's find a portal.
Hold on, did I take the health and the last?
Yeah, I did, I did, I did.
Whoop, that was close.
Oh, fuck off, plants.
Okay.
Let me in.
There's a portal.
The only question is, should I take it?
700 golds?
I think so.
I can dig back now.
So actually, it's fine.
Oh, wait, oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
He's here, he's here, he's here.
I can't prepare.
Okay, new plan.
I have an idea.
I kind of forgot I had this spell, but I'm gonna try now.
Oh, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude.
I know what to do, I know what to do, I know what to do.
Where is it?
There.
100 mana.
See, now I regret putting my remaining rocks and leave them behind.
This is it.
Yes, bitch!
Look at him.
Fucking hanging there.
Just like this homunculus is hanging.
Doesn't it kind of look like he's hanging?
And I hate these perks.
This is terrible.
I don't want any of this.
This is bad.
Boo.
But that right there, guys, was thinking on the fly.
I'm proud of it.
I will take this, because there's a trigger on it, and I do enjoy that.
Now I can reroll.
Lottery.
I do enjoy myself some lottery.
Thank you.
We are gonna be playing the lottery, and hopefully winning the lottery.
Now, I have 176 left.
I could buy something.
Something like...
Hold on, what if I put this on homing?
Explosive box on homing.
Is that gonna explode when it hits something?
Dude, I'm getting ideas here.
I'm getting ideas.
But dude, all I need to find now is unlimited spells, and then I'm set for life.
Then I am ready.
It's really all a man needs.
Put this one on the floor.
The other thing I wanted to try here, by the way, was to do this.
And then just have him walk through it.
I could even, like, make multiple, I guess, like that.
And then have him walk through it.
Hopefully it'll do enough damage.
That was my backup plan until I saw the homing.
When I saw the homing, I knew exactly what to do.
Yeah.
Okay, so let's make an actual wand.
Something that will do some damage.
What is my best sort of wand?
Just pure wand.
Let's see.
So this one has that.
That's worse.
And this one's also because...
It's worse because of the spread.
So this is my wand.
That is my wand.
If I do that, then it throws this one, that one, and it needs another one.
So we can do...
What is a good one?
Maybe that one?
So recharge is going.
Right.
Hold on.
So it shoots a green, then it shoots that.
Hmm.
I'm trying to make it shoot a little faster.
Or maybe I should just go back to my lightning bolt.
I mean, this chain bolt is honestly really good.
I can even do this.
Hey!
I just run out of mana real fast.
That's the issue with that.
This one would actually be really good for chain bolt.
If I can reduce the time it takes between shots.
Because it's quite long right now.
Uh, let's see here.
That adds...
Wait, what happens with this one?
Oh, it actually does sort of work.
Interesting.
Also, it is shuffled, so there's that.
I think I'm happy with that.
Hmm.
If only I had multiple chain bolts, that would be the dream.
So dude, I just had an idea.
Watch this.
Spark bolt with trigger.
And homing rock at the end.
Huh?
You shoot it wherever you want the rock to spawn.
How is that not insane?
Oh, I need unlimited spells immediately.
I need that shit immediately.
That would be so crazy.
For now though, I just want the best version of the chain bolt I can get.
And I think it may be that one.
As boring as that sounds.
0.38.
Actually.
Wait, it adds a bunch of castellae itself.
Yeah, you know what?
Let's leave it like that.
Then we have our cutter.
Very good.
Maybe I can put this on another one to make it even better.
But better here.
Okay.
And then here.
Oh yeah, definitely better.
So we leave that there.
This is our cutter.
On this one, I may actually just keep this set up here.
This is...
Oh, this is also shuffle.
So that's a bad idea.
So in that case, let's do this.
Remove that because it's shuffle and then put it down there.
That seems good.
And then I'm going to put this here.
Yeah, this is my setup right now.
That's what I'm going to roll with.
This is for the big enemies.
If I see a big guy, you know, that's what I'm using.
Yeah.
I only have a couple of shots of that, but it'll be glorious.
And now we need to dig.
Now we need to dig.
Oh, wait, I already did anger the gods though.
Oh, right.
I guess the message does pop multiple times.
The whole system with the angering the gods and stuff is still a little bit mysterious to me.
Whatever.
Okay, we are here.
So I have this.
Oh, my game just sort of.
You feel wary and dynamite symbols.
I don't know if I like that.
That scares me.
The issue I have here is that this is not long range.
And this place is very much long range.
I need to figure out how to deal with that, I guess.
It's kind of bad.
I didn't think about that.
See, this open space right here is bad for my spell.
Yeah, this is terrible.
But I make it work.
It's okay.
We just got to take it carefully here.
It's definitely a close quarters thing I have going for me.
I guess I do have my tablet as well in situations.
I may warrant it.
Don't you hit me with that.
Hold
on, how do I get rid of that?
That's annoying.
I don't really have a good spell to get rid of mines.
Berserkium.
I'm going to take that.
Why am I carrying around this?
Silver plus weird fungus.
Ooh, we could be getting high.
Ooh, fungal soil.
Fungal soil?
I'm going to keep it.
We only need one water potion, right?
Give me that.
Drink some of it.
Now we're going to town.
Whoa.
Oh, shit.
Nice.
Nice, nice, nice, nice.
Oh, I'm stuck, I'm stuck, I'm stuck.
Yeah, this one sucks for this place.
I got to be honest here, this is bad.
Oh my god, I can't dodge at all.
I'm terrible.
Also, that guy's going to spawn a bunch of small ones.
Yeah, there they come.
I'm actually dying here.
This is crazy.
Shit, man.
I can't do this.
What else can I do?
I guess I could go lightning bolt.
It's like the only real...
and then put it on a trigger, maybe.
What?
Trigger?
Wait a minute.
What's happening here?
Dude, wait a minute.
I've seen this before.
Get rid of this mine, please.
There we go.
Hold up a second here.
Gain access.
Dude.
I know what to do!
People.
Does this remind you of something?
It sure reminds me of something.
Hold on.
Look at this!
I almost killed myself!
Fuck!
Hold on, get rid of this.
Look at the eye!
Where have we seen that, huh?
Beneath the portals!
And what do the eyes contain?
Teleportation.
We need to find teleportation and put in there.
I bet something will happen.
Hold on, let me grab the snow here.
Drink the water.
Uh, get rid of...
Man, I hate my spells.
I hate my spells!
I hate my whole setup.
It's terrible.
Also, I need to heal.
I need to honestly go back.
Or not go back, go forward.
Through the portal.
Hold on.
I don't have any...
I'm just gonna go.
We're going through the portal.
This is a...
This is a pure disaster, what we have here.
This is bad.
Hold on, is this a worm?
Do we have a worm on the loose?
Oh no!
Can I get through here?
Of course I can.
Why am I forgetting I have this?
Just don't walk into the beam.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, I think we may be dead.
I have to play this insanely carefully.
I do have two rocks I can utilize.
Somehow those balls they shoot always manage to find their mark on me.
It's insane.
I lost some more health there.
Oh, I'm scared.
Fuck.
Holy shit!
So my eyes itchy.
Tell me there's a portal.
Oh, we've got a sniper.
Sir, that's for you.
I forgot the rock came out of the trigger.
Actually, the rock is here.
It's still active.
We can, we can push it around.
Boy, I didn't mean to shoot that!
Fuck!
What's that?
Kiba Skibi.
Damn it, man.
I wanted to use my thingy here.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
The good news is, I think I hear a portal.
Please, no enemies.
Go!
Close one.
Oh, but wait, wait, wait.
We got to take this immediately because the guy's here.
The dude is here.
And watch this.
Sir.
Oh!
Oh yeah?
You want to play like that?
Fuck you.
The gods are enraged.
I don't give a fuck.
Stay mad, bro.
Toxic immunity?
Gas fire.
Oh, I do like toxic immunity.
But dude, if I can find unlimited spells, that is my saving grace right now.
Hold on.
Let's just see what's on these ones.
Another homing?
All right, cool.
Yeah, I don't know about that.
I don't like these.
Let's see how the ones are.
Are they good or not?
Very shitty charge speed.
That's decent, I guess.
Although, very high recharge.
This one is...
Oh, it's two spells per cast.
I don't like these.
I don't like any of these.
Wait, always casts...
What is that?
La...
Yo.
Really?
Always casts lava to blood, huh?
Isn't that interesting?
I intended to buy that.
I hate this sound.
We gotta get rid of this.
Stop making that sound.
I think I'll take toxic, because goddamn do I hate toxic.
Fuck that noise.
Oh yeah, right.
We have perk lottery!
Guys, I don't think I like this.
I'm gonna save up for re-rolling that.
Yeah.
I do wonder what happens then.
Will we get two more new or do we get three new?
I guess we'll have to see.
That's a bit of an interesting situation there.
Okay, now, I think I want to buy this wand.
But it is not that expensive.
It's 50% off.
Let's do it.
The reason I say this is if we discover...
We can make like a lava to blood wand.
You know, that's...
We always carry around, and we can do that thing.
That sounds pretty cool to me.
So where is it?
It's that one.
So on here, we can put...
Like bouncing burst, I guess.
Just something.
And the cool thing is, this will always...
Convert lava to blood.
Like if I shoot this, and it hits some lava, bam, blood.
Right?
That's crazy.
I need to make an actual wand that doesn't suck now.
It may just be this.
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
We are going to be in an easy base now.
So we have to think close quarters.
Close quarters combat.
CQC.
Maybe chain bolt is the way to go here.
Chain bolt is kind of dope in this place.
But the vertical barrier too?
We can make some fun happen.
It's not an amazing damage or anything, but it'll get me by, you know?
And then we could have a rock for emergency.
Not a terrible idea.
Short range homing, also short range homing.
Okay.
What happens if I add two short range homing?
I wonder if that changes anything.
Probably not.
Now magic bolt.
Maybe we can make something with that on one of these wands.
Maybe this one.
Is that our new?
Oh man, the recharge on this is absolutely terrible.
Yeah, that ain't fun.
That's not good.
This one though, 0.03, 0.80, 0.38.
Does have a high mana charge speed.
If I can...
Wait a minute, where's my...
If I do this...
Right.
If I had a double...
I guess because there's already four spells per cast, so it's a little bit weird.
I don't even know what I'm trying here, guys.
I'm just sort of...
Wait, what's been shot?
Maybe we go missile.
Magic arrow.
How does this feel?
It's almost like a bouncing burst.
It's like a better version of a bouncing burst.
Right?
Feels like it.
I think I'm going with this, guys.
It's going to be lightning bolt, because it is a consistent damage output.
I just got to be careful with it.
Like, it is there.
It's good.
It's a good spell, man.
You can't deny it.
It's there.
And then we're going to have a...
We're going to have a rock.
Yeah.
We're going to have a homing rock, just in case.
That sounds cool to me.
We can always come back here and change things, too.
So that's dope.
All right, it's digging time.
Oh, I forgot to make it digging.
Oh yeah, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Uh, I did a little mistake-y.
This wand.
I, um...
Now I'm confused.
Let me put these here.
Put that there.
And then put...
Yeah, maybe I don't use the rock right now.
Yeah, not yet.
Although I could get rid of the vertical bear...
No, I want to try that in combat.
We're going to try the vertical barrier.
I'm so indecisive here, it's insane.
There we go.
And then I will take this, put it up here, grab that, do that, and then do this there.
So whenever I use this, it's going to also turn lava into blood, apparently.
So that's funny.
I am going to do this.
Yeah, just for safety.
I'm actually so scared of this.
It scares me, man.
All right, let's go, let's go.
Time to make the gods angry.
The gods are very angry with you.
What does that mean?
Are they going to send an upgraded set?
Are they going to send a whole fucking pack of wolves?
All right.
Who's in here?
Get rid of that one.
Oh, see, there we go.
See, this is the kind of thing where we want to use the electrical thingy.
Boing!
Oh, it's not far enough.
It's so good against the mechanical opponents.
It's a solid weapon.
Like, it's solid, but it's dangerous, you know?
How dare you?
Yep.
Come here.
Oh, I'm sad we didn't find a broken wand.
That is pure sadness.
What do you want?
I have to remember to switch away from the wand because I'm scared of electrifying any surface.
Frendo!
I don't have pheromone!
I forgot about these guys.
Oh, dude, we got to find pheromone.
Holy shit.
That just gave me a lot of hope.
No way.
Is that pheromone?
Don't go into it!
Oh, I'm sorry, guys.
I'm sorry.
For ruining your party.
That is not pheromone, but it is flammoxium.
Yeah, how about no...
Nobody wants flammoxium in their system.
Ouch!
Prendo, heal me.
Just do it anyway.
I know we're sworn enemies, but still.
Can you do me a favor?
What?
Is he shooting?
Oh, God.
I'm being swarmed.
Gotta be careful here.
Why is my range so low?
Look, they're healing each other.
Oh, man.
I guess if I could intercept the heal, I could take the heal, you know?
It's a little bit risky, though.
Come here.
Ow!
Motherfucker.
There's a guy below me, but watch this.
Oh, my God.
I gotta find pheromone.
Oh, how did you get up here?
What the fuck happened?
Insane.
My guy teleported up here somehow.
Get rid of explosives.
I am so scared of accidentally firing my electrical bolt instead of my...
this one, you know?
Oh, motherfucker!
See, there I fired the wrong one.
I wanted to fire that.
Oh, yeah, get fucked.
Oh, he's healing him.
Aw, friendo.
Come on.
That's disappointing.
You're on my side, damn it.
Oh, he died.
Very nice.
He did burn alive after all.
Uh-oh.
Holy shit.
Lots of molten metal.
Not exactly something you want to see.
Oh, that's nice.
It took a 90-degree turn there.
What the hell is that?
Toxic sludge?
Oh, but wait, I'm immune.
Hey!
Not that I need it for anything.
But kind of dope, I guess.
And a wand.
Oh, my God.
Okay, okay, okay.
I want to get rid of that bomb.
And I want to get up here.
Oh, yeah.
Bathe me in toxic.
So nice.
Fuck off.
Why did that happen?
Because there's 31 degrees of spread on the wand.
I put the lightning bolt on.
Fuck me.
That's why.
Off.
No!
I had to calm down there.
That was very annoying.
Fucking Ukuskivi of all things.
Can you believe it?
Okay.
That just pissed me off.
That was annoying.
Of all the things to be in that chest.
My sworn enemy object of all time.
The Ukuskivi.
And I was stunned to oblivion.
Not much I could have done there.
Where did all this water come from?
Oh, that's the pipe thing.
Isn't it?
Okay.
Wait, what?
Okay, never mind.
Look at that.
It just drips water.
That is such a weird modifier.
I mean, I don't mind it.
That means less toxic for me.
And that makes me happy.
Actually, there's a little hole there.
I could have shot my way in.
These enemies are some of the worst in the entire game.
Surprise!
It's a special gift for you guys down there.
Like, look how much I have to clean up after one enemy.
Pretty much contaminated this entire region.
And now we have polymorphine, which is something everyone inspires to have on their person.
Isn't it?
Just the best thing ever.
Oh, I'm gonna go here.
No, I'm not.
There's a wand though.
Not fast enough.
Actually, you know, this is kind of a good wand.
It shoots three of these really fast.
So it's like, how much do they do?
Three damage.
That's like nine damage guaranteed when you hit.
Also, I need to get through here.
I don't want to use a bomb.
I'm gonna go around.
No!
Oh my god.
That was some more polymorphine there that just got broken.
And now it's everywhere.
Oh, what is this now?
Okay, nice.
Wasn't that bad.
I'll take it.
God's yes.
Is that...
Is that the gas thing?
I'm not entirely sure.
But I'm gonna get in there for sure.
Oh, collapsed mines right there.
You.
That's a...
I mean, I think this is the gas.
Another bomb.
That would be lovely.
Go!
Oh god.
Oh god!
It was eating through the floor and fell on my head.
That could have been a lot worse.
Good thing it didn't get worse.
There's a dude down here.
We got some flasks or potions.
I mean, I can afford to spend some bombs, I guess.
But no, let's walk around first.
That's a trap.
Is that a...
Dude, that's another poison.
We're not poison.
It's more like acid, isn't it?
Close.
Hmm.
Man, the arrows.
I wonder if they're actually any good.
Like, can you make something great out of that?
Like, imagine an arrow spammer.
Something goes brrrr.
But with arrows.
That could be kind of cool to try, right?
I think so, at least.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Not that guy.
That's the worst.
Ah, Hemis!
Sorry, sorry, Hemis.
What's all this gold?
Where did that come from?
Uh, I will kill you.
Nope.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay.
Shit!
Run, run, run, run, run.
Get away from that.
What's that?
Levitation?
Why not?
I feel like it's been a while since I've seen a levitation potion.
What's up, Barney?
Give me that.
Okay, I really want to kill this guy here.
He's annoying me.
What if he hits himself with that projectile?
Does a cloud follow him around?
Nice!
Noice.
Yo!
Holy concentrated mana.
Pheromone!
Oh, dude.
We're getting that pheromone.
It's gonna save our asses later.
Like, think about it.
If I had pheromone last run, I most likely would have survived that incident.
Because I would have been full health.
You know, so something small will really add up later on.
Uh, where should I deposit this?
Maybe just down here.
I'm never gonna go down here, I don't think.
God damn it!
I spilled on myself.
You bastard!
Since that I was polymorphed, huh?
And you came all this way just to ruin my day.
But I didn't let you.
Throw it down here.
Nice.
Let me fill up my water.
Okay.
And then we grab the pheromone.
What is this one?
Oh, right, levitation.
Uh, hold on.
There's also blood and constant...
There's all kinds of stuff down here.
Oh, flammoxium.
Oh, the yikes.
I, I, no, I just want the pheromone!
Oh, that's fucked up.
This is fucked up.
I have trouble moving my character.
I think it's mostly pheromone now.
Hopefully, otherwise I'll have to empty the rest out.
Wait, is that tripping concentrated mana out of that pipe?
Another polymorphine potion?
What's going on here?
Blood potion?
What?
Whoa!
Is that ambrosia?
Bro, what is going on here?
Why are there so many potions?
This is a complete mess.
Look how much shit is in here.
Pheromone, steam, levitation, water, flammoxium, peat, and fire.
What a combo.
We gotta cleanse that immediately.
Out with all the crap.
Okay, that's mostly pheromone.
Now we only have pheromone.
Perfect.
That's what I was looking for.
Burn that.
Oh, you don't.
This asshole was sitting there waiting for...
Also, I gotta grab a tablet before we go on.
Very important.
It's on the checklist of things to do so we can deal with Zed.
Okay, not too bad.
Look at that, man.
Clean.
Don't go in the portal by accident.
53 HP, that's not great.
Another one!
What is going on?
This is insanity.
This guy is supremely annoying.
Oh, he died, good.
That is the most amount of those guys I've seen.
In such a short, uh, period of time.
Again!
This is unreal.
And frocks everywhere.
Oh, no, this is bad.
This is really bad.
Somehow I came out of that without losing any HP.
That's insane.
Wait, my potion is steam!
What?
I somehow turned all my water into steam in my potion.
I have never seen that.
Weird.
Let's empty that.
Okay.
Oh, no.
That way.
Go.
I really need water.
Just any amount.
I'll take that.
Oh, shit.
Man, this guy is good.
I'm gonna blow him up.
Nice.
That's how you do it.
Barney!
Okay, here we go.
Water.
I wonder if the water bottle turns into steam if I...
Oh, you know what?
I think I know what it was.
I must have picked up fire in that bottle somehow.
I must have made it boil.
Oh, this is a special horta.
Oh, okay.
Found the roots.
Oh, a whole family.
Ah, this is dead end.
But look at this.
Now we just need some light.
We have enough bombs to do funny things.
Yeah.
I'm gonna go east.
This has not been a super good hemisphere so far.
I need more hearts.
If I'm to become a powerful magician...
I need better ones, man.
And more hearts.
Wait, what was that?
Something's burning.
You hear it?
Up here?
What's going on there?
Oh, it's you.
You piece of shit.
I'm gonna run you a bath.
And then you will come down here and have a wash.
Can I get rid of that coal?
Yeah, kill yourself.
Oh, never mind.
Come here.
Hey!
Pussy.
Join me in the bath.
All right, fine, I'll kill you.
I just don't want to release all the lava!
All right, fine, that works.
She wasn't too bad.
In search of hearts.
Also, that used to be a trap.
I triggered it.
That's Ambrosia down there.
That's lava.
Oh, look at all this crap.
What a mess this is.
Wow.
But the good news is we have pheromone now.
And look at all the water.
The water just keeps pouring.
Like it never stops.
Holy crap.
Dude, this level is filled with the hardest enemies.
It's crazy.
This is like the sixth guy.
Rainmaker or whatever.
Rainman.
Wait, did that guy just kill himself?
I guess that wand must be dangerous.
What kind of wand is that?
I'm curious.
Oh, he teleported himself into some water most of the time.
Most likely.
That is a fantastic wand to find.
Thank you.
That is lovely.
That's lovely that.
Lovely.
It's actually a great start now.
I shall not shit talk this hemisphere anymore.
Quickly jump to the top of the ranks.
Got him.
Let's grab the tablet.
That's on our to-do list.
A blood potion I can get rid of.
Thanks.
Okay.
Should I go down there?
Can I go down there?
I can.
Yeah, nothing there.
Oh, I love having the teleport.
I gotta get used to having it though.
What's that?
Acceleration.
Oh, it's so comfortable having this.
No, I'm gonna keep my levitation.
Yup.
Because you know what?
We can go on top of the...
We can grab the heart now.
Levitation allows us to do that.
Well, we still gotta dig, but we can dig from above, I guess.
Asshole.
Bit me in the face.
Wow, guys.
Have you ever seen this many in this place?
This is absolutely wild.
It's like the eighth or something.
Or seventh.
Whoa, that was close.
Okay, I'm pretty good at dealing with them now, actually.
I have become proficient at it, I must say.
Whoop, wrong spell.
Accidents like that happen.
Look at that.
A little family of hemisses.
Warms the heart, doesn't it?
Unfortunately, I will have to murder them.
Why, you may ask?
Because.
That works.
Money is the answer.
Also, dude, fucked levitation.
We have teleport.
That's another way to get up there, of course.
Oh, I want to get up there.
I'm gonna make a hole.
Boing.
Still have four bombs left.
Okay.
So, we should be able to bomb our way in.
Maybe from here and then there.
Had to do a sneeze.
Okay, let's go.
Oh yeah, buried deep.
Lovely.
Oh wait, can I launch the bomb in here, though?
Can I break the snow?
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Shit.
That's the issue, that's what I feared.
Uh, hmm.
If I put it up here, maybe I have enough time.
Nope.
Oh, that's fucking annoying.
There's no way.
Come on.
Can I really not...
launch it somehow?
I have an idea, I have an idea.
No, no, no, no, no.
Don't roll down.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Stay, stay, stay.
Come on, you bastard.
Stay.
Come on.
Oh, that's so annoying.
Wow.
Okay, that, that actually...
Wait a minute.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
It
was almost there.
Yes.
Now watch.
Fuck yeah, dude.
Beautiful.
Holy shit.
That thing went far, huh?
Now we move on.
That, that got a little personal at the end there.
I really wanted to get that fucking part.
I think it's time for us to leave.
Let's go.
Yup.
Something's going on below me.
What do we have?
Boxes.
Hello.
Black holes, not bad.
And Dunamit.
Ooh, guys.
Perk lottery.
And that together would be immaculate.
Ah well.
But that's also very nice.
That is also...
I wonder if that ever, ever worse than the first try.
Maybe.
I don't know if I ever tried that or experienced that happening.
I will replace the shopping want.
Thank you very much.
Oh, I can't even use these.
Oh, I can use it here.
That is now my black hole.
And then we got to find some actual damage.
Shit.
I mean, maybe we're just bouncing burst for now.
We are just in the cold pits.
But here's the question.
How do we kill Zed?
That is the big question.
We got a...
Oh, no.
Hmm.
Wait a minute, I need to think.
Oh, dude.
I could make a huge trap with those and blow him the fuck up.
That's the plan.
Oh, we're making a huge trap, baby.
Oh, this is going to be glorious.
Okay, hold on.
Let me just see here.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
I'm even going to put some here.
I do wonder if stacking them will do anything different.
Maybe it helps, maybe not.
Like that.
I have a little surprise for you, Zed.
Okay.
I may also put some here.
Just in case he comes up here and he didn't die for some reason.
And I can blow those up.
And then I'm also going to purchase this one right here to get the dynamite to blow them up.
Yes, that seems good.
Let me just double check.
It works as expected.
Seems to work as expected.
Perfect.
Although it is kind of dangerous to stand here and throw dynamite, isn't it?
Like that, that is...
Can I...
Okay, thank God.
We can kick this down.
Let me kick these a little more to the right, actually.
This is a bit precarious what's going on here, I understand.
I understand.
Now...
Could I perhaps...
Let's say it doesn't work.
Do I have another option to do something?
I don't think so.
There's not really anything else I can do here.
Oh, but you know what the good news is?
I have teleport wand.
So if shit hits this fan and I can't kill him and I need to make a getaway, I can probably teleport past him and out of here.
That's the plan.
That's my getaway plan.
Also, I'm going to quickly take a piss before this happens.
I'll be right back.
Are you ready?
So let me just run through the process here.
I'm going to anger him.
And then when he spawns, I'm going to instantly dynamite him and hopefully he will fucking die.
And if that fails, then I get...
You know what?
Actually, hold on.
I have an idea.
The way I'm going to anger him...
Oh, I guess this is a nice way to test this anyway.
I'm just going to destroy some brickwork down here, drain the water, and have an escape here.
Is that smart though?
Let me think about it.
Yeah, it's decently smart, I would say.
Yeah, that's okay.
That seems good.
Okay, here we go.
Stay mad, bro.
Oh, yeah, he's angry.
Okay, get ready, get ready.
Here we go, here we go.
Hey, Seth.
Seth's dead, baby.
Seth's dead.
That's fantastic.
How are you doing over there, Seth?
Unbelievable.
Come on, blow the last one up, please.
There we go.
I wonder how much does this do?
125 damage explosive.
Damn, that's a lot.
That is a lot.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Okay, we are in the cold, baby.
The quest continues.
This is actually a decent wand.
I kind of like it.
But this one is also very okay.
49, 6 slots.
I'm going to leave it for now.
Hold on, actually.
0.15, 0.37.
This was 0.23, 0.17.
You know, I'm going to actually exchange it immediately.
Put this here.
There we go.
And then I'm going to pick up these spells again.
That's the plan.
Wait.
There we go.
On this, I want to use these.
No, I don't want to use those.
I hate those.
It's also going to produce a bunch of toxic shit everywhere.
I don't like that.
Oh, yeah, look at this.
It's much more sustained.
Sustainability is important.
Oh, wait, we need a teleport wand.
Maybe get rid of this one.
How good is this wand?
Yeah, there's a teleport wand right there.
Very nice.
And we have this, that, dynamite, black holes.
What more do you want?
Not much.
I'm happy.
I'm satisfied.
I'm a happy camber.
Concentrated mana potion.
It could be cool.
We have to...
Oh, hold on.
How do we get in there without destroying absolutely everything?
Probably we don't.
Not with what I currently have.
Ouch!
Assholes.
Uh-oh.
Oh, get out of there.
That's a death trap.
Yeah, you're too fat to get in.
Wait, did I hit him?
Oh, Jesus.
That took a while.
Man, my wand sucks for this place.
Even just the second zone, you do kind of want something a little better.
Let's see what we got here.
Maybe this is our salvation.
It is not.
Not much salvation there.
Whoopsie daisy.
Where'd you go?
Like a little mini boss.
Another wand.
It's so freeing to know that you have a place where you can change your wand.
It is actually amazing.
I'm so glad I decided to actually face Zed instead of just either avoiding him or trying to make peace with him.
I mean, if that pops up, maybe I'll even take it just because it's such a
good...
Okay, that calls for a black hole.
Or does it?
No, it doesn't.
We are gonna dynamite.
We have so much dynamite.
Yo, now we're talking.
I like what I'm seeing.
The wand is actually not bad if I'm just going with magic arrows, I guess.
Although, point three is still kind of high for something that should shoot fast.
Um, I mean, I'm gonna go back with it.
We gotta get that quickness.
What's it called?
Quick recharge?
Reduce recharge, right?
So it's pretty much just...
Oh, but there's also a wand here.
Oh, I think I checked that one already.
Yes, yes.
So just remember, when I find that, it's a little higher up.
And I keep forgetting I have teleport wand.
So now I want to put this here.
And maybe just use these.
This does like 10 damage per shot.
Much better.
Hell yeah.
Me likey.
I'll take that as well.
The wand though, not a fan.
Although, hold on a second.
Hey, oh, but we're low on mana there.
Would have been so good though.
3.31.
Wait a minute.
I mean, that's not bad.
Actually not bad.
But it is kind of nice to just be able to sustain it for longer, no?
And I do a decent amount of damage.
I'm gonna save this reduce recharge.
Yeah, I'm saving it.
Until we have a better wand.
Also, this teleport wand is not making me happy because it has a...
I can't spam it.
Gotta wait like half a second, which is like an eternity, of course.
Thanks.
Oh yeah.
Feels better too.
Gold for me.
Now we're at the edge.
How did that not blow up the gunpowder?
I can shotgun people flying all around, but I'm dealing with it.
Okay, that seems like a dead end.
Oh, that guy has a wand.
I'm scared.
What are you gonna shoot at me?
Okay, that's not too bad, I think.
Trying to flank me in the meanwhile.
Did I get him?
I think I may have gotten him.
Cluster bolts.
I don't like that.
Nope.
I reject the cluster bolts.
Oh, shit.
Dude, I'm good at aiming.
I just nailed those guys.
Dripping lava.
Hello.
Do I want that?
The wand is not bad.
This is actually a good wand.
0.13, 0.47, 2, 20, 48.
And it has a bunch of those things, which could be nice.
I may just take it and go back with it.
That is not bad.
And then I will take this, take that.
I'll take all of these.
This can go away.
And then we put these on here.
Come on.
Let's see here.
Dum, dum, dum, dum.
Okay.
But with this on,
much faster.
Maybe you don't need this many of these luminous drills.
Let's have two of them.
Seems like an okay amount.
Ooh, wait a minute.
The spread is big on it.
That ain't good.
That actually sucks.
How's this wand?
Oh, they're all kind of bad.
Well, at least I got some luminous drills out of it.
I'm going to go back and take my old wand.
If I remember where it is.
Somewhere over here, I think.
Oh god, am I already lost?
No, this is the way.
Is that it?
Yes.
What's up here?
Oh, not much.
So stuff like this, I kind of want to blow it.
Just to get the money.
And I pretty much have infinite TNT.
So why shouldn't I blow it?
Okay, we're back here.
Let's try this.
See what we got.
But do I do have a feeling we're close to the fungal caverns.
A chest.
Thank god there was no ukuscivian there.
It's an inanimate fucking object.
And somehow it still managed to murder me multiple times.
Okay, nothing there.
Anything up here?
Wait.
What the fuck is this?
Oh, I made this.
Forgot about that.
I made that hole.
Oh, it does not go in that.
Okay, you know what?
Let's blow this up.
Can we get in there without blowing up the flask?
Damn it.
Ah well.
Whatever.
Ooh!
The shots bounce off surfaces too.
Oh yeah.
Wait, did he just...
Dude.
He's actually throwing different liquids.
Wait a minute.
Look, gunpowder.
He just threw oil at himself.
Dude, can you throw me a...
I was about to say pheromone, thank you.
But throw it to me.
Oh, he's my friend now.
Because he pheromoned himself.
That's actually amazing.
You idiot.
You accidentally became my friend.
But that's fine.
Hold on, I actually do have some pheromone on me.
I can grab more.
You want to maybe...
Here we go, here goes.
Thank you!
Thank you for that, friend!
Look, he just gave me a pheromone.
That's for you then.
We trade.
You get to...
You know what, I'm gonna murder you.
For that.
And then he...
Man.
You can like farm potions off of this guy if you do it in a smart way.
Did you notice how the flasks didn't get destroyed when they hit the slime?
Ow!
How the fuck did I get hit there?
Such a measly enemy.
Actually, I want to get in there.
I'm gonna be lazy here.
No, I'm not.
I'm not lazy.
Go!
Do not succumb to laziness.
Light.
Firebolt with trigger.
Nah.
Ow!
Burned myself a little bit there.
Dude, critting is actually insane.
I wonder how good a crit build would be.
You know?
Like always being bloodied and all that.
Like it does like five times the damage.
Oh, shit.
Like instead of 10, I did 50 when I crit.
That's significant.
With the right perks, you could maybe do something there.
One more.
Stop spawning children.
God, it's annoying.
So annoying.
Okay, it's dead.
Look at all that lava we made.
That got a little scary.
Oh!
Oh, no.
Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope.
This is bad.
I feel like this is spiraling right now.
It's one of those...
I can feel it, you know?
The spiral is real.
And there's a guy...
There's a mage.
Got him!
Important.
Another mage.
Let's get rid of this fucking toxic shit.
I think that guy will teleport me if he hits me.
Because he's teleporting around himself.
Come here.
Yeah, look, teleportation.
He is full of that.
Oh, the fungal caverns.
A very risky but high reward place.
It feels humid?
That's good though, right?
There's one in there.
I can get there.
I have black holes.
Hold on.
I do have teleport too, so...
If worst comes to worst, I can always teleport away.
I may just quickly venture in there.
You know, just have a quick look.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Let's kill that guy.
He bleeds tele...
Wow!
Oh, that's what's going on.
Okay.
Cool, actually.
Kind of dope.
Why is this pheromone potion triangular?
Wait, is that a superior one?
It contains 200 percent!
Holy shit, I never realized that.
I think I had a triangular potion before.
Very cool.
That's levitation.
We're not afraid of levitation.
Nah, whoop, I didn't mean to drop down.
And that's about as far as I'm willing to go into the caverns.
And I'm out.
Am I completely out though?
Let me think.
50 HP.
I can always come back.
Oh, hold on, hold on, hold on.
The god is going to be there.
We have to be ready.
We got to get something ready for this.
I can't just go in there immediately.
Good thing I just remembered that.
We got to prepare.
Oh, look, look, look, look.
Hey!
My dude is...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Please don't, don't throw.
No.
God damn it, man.
As soon as you let your guard down, this game fucks you in the ass.
It's insane.
This fucking game here, man.
I shit you not.
Like, I go from being frozen to being kicked around.
Having no more, what's it called?
Levitation energy.
So I can't get out and then I get frozen again.
It's just what a combination that just took place there.
Holy shit.
That felt terrible.
Okay, give me this at least.
It's a nice consolation present.
You know what?
I'll take the tablet too.
Thank you.
Put it there.
T is my tablet keybind.
I can't believe I just fucking died like that.
Oh, man.
That was such a good run as well.
I killed Zed.
It was awesome.
I was ready to kill him again.
Things were going great.
Until they weren't.
I'm fucking tired of being in these mines.
I shit you not.
Like, there is a bit of a tediousness in just having to go through this place and collect the money and all that.
So there's a chest in there.
I'm taking it.
Oh, a bomb.
How lovely.
And this guy's throwing shit.
What are you gonna throw?
Throw whatever.
I'm gonna pick it up.
Come here.
Think I'm scared?
Come on.
Okay, never mind.
Wow, asset is deadly.
That was from a hundred to zero in zero seconds.
Damn.
Okay, those guys are more dangerous than I thought.
Yeah.
I will get this tablet up here now.
In fact, I should have just used a tablet on them.
Why didn't I do that?
I really gotta implement that as like a baseline thing.
It needs to be muscle memory to just whip out the old tablet and go to town, you know?
Oh my god.
Okay, that works.
Oh, what is this recharge?
That is disgusting.
Ew.
Look at that.
Almost hit me in the face.
Okay, it's almost out.
I'll wait for this energy.
What is the mana charge on this?
Wow, that's terrible.
Damn.
Damn, dude.
That's really bad.
Oh, I didn't have enough mana.
Shit.
Come on.
Look at this.
The sun has gone down in the meanwhile.
Or meantime.
That's how long this is taking me.
Okay, it's almost there.
Look how dark it is now.
Get out of the way.
There we go.
I had a hit massager on my table and it was annoying me.
Yes!
That was a lot of work, but I got it.
What do we have here?
Acceleration.
I don't remember if that will actually put out fires.
But I am gonna consume all of this.
And then we'll speedrun, find some water.
Oh, nice.
We actually have a nice DPS wand here.
Yay, more of these.
Awesome.
I wonder...
So there's a Pergus wealth that says faster movement.
I wonder if that's like having this effect on, but all the time.
Flammoxium.
Sure, why not?
Let's just have it.
What if I drink it?
I'm simply confused.
Okay.
Gotcha.
Hey, you there.
Dude, dodging is actually really comfortable when you're fast.
Maybe that is a perk worth taking.
It does feel good.
It is weird, though, that I don't go as far when I go up and down, like...
The difference between X and Y movement here is very jarring.
What's that?
Gold pouch?
Actually!
No way!
What?
That's awesome!
Oh my goodness!
That's a lot of gold!
Look at that!
Oh, wait, did I just pick it up again?
Oops.
Wow, a thousand gold!
That's a lot.
Oh, we don't have any water.
Gotta get some of that.
Where do we have water?
Wait, can I just pick anything up with this pouch?
Yeah, I got some coal, I got some soil and grass.
Can I take out flames with soil?
Oh, no, probably not coal is the best idea for that, huh?
That probably just stokes the flame.
Not very thought through there.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Unstable teleportation.
I don't know about that, but yeah, maybe.
I mean, it's a flask, right?
So I could take it.
Just need some water first.
What's going on here?
A chest for me!
Oh, no.
Oh, very cool!
Now, the best way to get in there is probably up here.
Oh, this one is way better at this.
Ah, hold on.
Don't want an ukuskivi in there.
Or a bomb, for that matter.
Yes.
No, I didn't get it.
Hold on, let me just confirm.
So, look at this!
You see this?
This is the exact same thing we saw in, uh, uh, Snowy Depths.
Look at the exact same model as well.
We have to fill that with teleportation.
Something will happen, dude.
If we see that, I...
Okay, we gotta...
You know what?
There actually was some unstable teleportation.
Maybe we can use that.
Wait, how did he die?
I didn't hit him.
Did I hit him?
I guess I must have.
Oh, he's out hunting.
Uh-oh.
Oh, I'm so slow now without the acceleration.
I could get used to the acceleration, actually.
That's really nice.
Look at this.
Two of them.
Oh, my god.
Oh, my god, oh, my god.
Yep, it's getting dangerous.
This is for you.
At least he died.
Lost too much HP there, man.
And I haven't found any water in this level.
How is that actually real?
Like, what's going on here?
Like, either we have too much water?
It's overflowing, literally, or nothing at all.
Where is the water?
Can I spit the fish in Vasahab?
No ambition.
Do I even want to fight this dude?
Maybe I just leave him.
Water!
Let's go!
Now I want to fight him.
I'm going to super soak him.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, hold on.
I should go grab the tablet.
Fall in the hole, fall in the hole.
Ah, you asshole.
I may actually die here.
I have no way out.
I have no way out!
Oh, thank God.
I had to use the big guns there.
Worth it, though.
That was a bit of a difficult spot to be in.
What's up, Hamis?
You see this?
I've seen that before.
So many times.
I'm going to blow it up.
I'm sorry, Hamis.
Today's your day.
And you go to heaven.
To Hamis heaven.
Oh, yeah, he died.
Quite a lot there.
He died so much.
Whoa, asshole.
40 HP.
It's not going well.
Yeah, this is bad.
What is over here?
Oh, there's a chest there.
That's exciting.
Ah, use this.
I wonder!
He was just about to pick it up, too, that asshole.
Ping pong path.
And some rocks.
Not terrible.
I can dig it.
I like it.
In fact, I love that shit.
I am thinking ping pong path.
Maybe with the healing spell.
I don't...
Did I try that before?
It may have.
I definitely tried some kind of a special path.
And I made it work.
At some point.
I just don't remember how exactly I did all that.
There's a big dude in there.
I don't care about him.
He can stay in there.
Fine with me.
Dude, I have 1800 gold!
Maybe it's time to just go through the portal.
And re-roll a million times.
Until I find...
Tinkering with wands.
That's what you really want.
Or unlimited spells.
Now that I found a rock.
Wouldn't be too bad.
Did I try that one?
Wait a minute.
I think I must have.
Yeah.
Hold on.
I want to go a little more to the left first.
We still have 32 HP.
And there's a chest, too.
Ah, please don't die now.
What the fuck is this?
There's sand in here.
Is that pheromone?
I think that's pheromone.
We need that.
Nope, it's persurfium.
That's fine, too.
I like that.
Let's drink some of it.
Toxic sludge you.
Oh!
Hello!
There's a worm!
I took care of his ass.
Hold on.
There was a chest here somewhere.
Wait, where was that chest?
Uh-oh.
Oh, watch this!
Hey, sir!
Fuck you!
Sincerely, everybody in the world.
Very nice.
That was beautiful, wasn't it?
Now, there was a chest here somewhere.
Ah, there it is.
Okay, so I gotta get up there.
I may just...
go in this...
Goddammit.
Oh, does this even go through rock?
Open.
Oh, wait.
Oh, it's wood.
Okay, it's gonna burn.
Do we want that?
I don't want that.
No!
Dammit!
How am I gonna get in?
Maybe there's an explosive somewhere.
I could fire here and burn that, but it's not gonna get through this part.
So I need some extra.
Oh, dude, I have an idea.
I have an idea.
Is this actually gonna work?
Hold on.
I'm picking up all of this.
Oh, yeah.
This is an experiment.
Let's see if it works.
This is powerful enough to go through at least a little bit of dirt here.
Oh, but wait.
How do we ignite it?
Oh, wait.
Fire, of course.
Ah, it's not enough.
We gotta find an explosive.
Hey.
Oh,
very good.
Here we go.
Exactly what we needed.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes!
Okay.
Uh, I need to get it above.
Oh my god, what a, what a kick!
Uh, I need to go to, I need to let it go up here.
Preferably.
Almost broke the potion.
Maybe this will be enough if it blows like this part away too.
It's hard to say.
Oh, I can, oh, that's actually very useful.
I can stand on it and still like, it doesn't hit me.
Oh, this, this changes a lot.
Hold on.
Straight up and then a little that way.
No, fuck.
Yes!
No!
Ah!
Yes!
Insane skills!
And now I have to, uh, how do I, I took this, I took the chance.
And no more now, because I'm scared of it.
Okay.
It's time to move on.
No, no, no, wait, it's not.
We need a tablet.
That's one of the rules.
If we have to engage set, we gotta get a tablet.
Hemis.
2,200 monies in the hemisphere.
That is unheard of.
Let me tell you that.
You don't see that every day.
Oh!
Okay, I thought I saw something scary.
But alas, it was nothing.
Could use more water.
We could die here if we're not careful.
Okay, here we go.
We take the tablet and we leave.
Uh, we should get rid of the flammoxium, obviously.
Let's throw that in the lava and see what happens.
She sits on top, huh?
Cool.
All right.
Flammoxium on lava.
No!
Why?
What?
Uh...
Oh, wait.
Hold on.
What do we have?
Quick, quick.
Come on, homing, homing, homing, homing, homing, homing, homing, homing.
Homing?
Sawblade orbit?
Okay, hold on.
Oh, the game is paused.
Let's think about this.
No shuffle.
It shoots fireballs.
And there's sawblade orbit on it.
I can kill him with that.
I can kill him with this, guys.
No matter!
All right, bitch.
Say, how do you mom for me?
Shit, my HP.
He needs to come over here.
Oh, no, oh, no, oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Quick, poke.
Down again.
Fucking worms!
God damn it, man.
That was so sad.
What a sadness.
Fucking, now I'm back here again, man.
Fuck you, said.
I
am very displeased at this moment.
Very displeased.
What's that?
Oh, at least we have pheromone.
That's something.
But it's not going to come and use until he's a base.
Give me your money.
Oh, there's fire dudes everywhere, too.
Look at that, though.
What's going on here?
What?
Oh, torch.
Oh, but hold on, this is useless.
I can't edit my wants anyway.
But I guess I can use this later.
Okay.
I think...
Maybe...
Maybe the...
I think maybe this one has a shot at killing, said.
So I'm going to buy that when I have the money.
And we can also...
No, the torch is useless.
Because we cannot edit once now.
Later.
Okay, so here's the plan.
I'm going to pheromone this dude.
No, I'm not.
I'm going to grab the tablet.
It's tablet time, baby.
Not that way.
Go around.
This way.
Don't let it be a dead end.
Fuck.
Oh, I actually do have that.
Explosive box.
Now, that's a big explosion, too.
Just do it.
I take the chance.
In fact, there's no water there, so Ukuskivi is not going to do much.
If it comes out.
And if there's a bomb, usually it takes a while for it to blow, right?
So I'm actually okay.
If it's in water, that's really dangerous.
Because if that's an Ukuskivi, then you're fucked.
Then it's just over.
I've had first-hand experience with that, let me tell you.
Ukuskivi...
How the hell do I go to the right and grab my tablet?
What?
I'm gonna blow up everything.
Yeah, I'm blowing up shit.
I've had enough.
Going down here, and I'm blowing.
Boink.
Oh, can I not?
Aw, what?
What?
All right, fine.
Are you kidding?
That's unreal.
Oh, that's an explosion.
And now I get to go, and there's a wand.
But I'm going here first.
I should grab that water.
But what about my pheromone?
I could store that here, actually.
That's a perfect spot.
If we need it, we come back later with another potion and grab it.
Now we have a water potion.
Here we are.
That's it.
The deadly weapon has been acquired.
I gotta say, killing people with that is actually hilarious.
Who else wants some?
You want some?
Hey.
Amazing.
Um, I guess I'll go around.
You know what I just noticed?
Something that I haven't appreciated, but look at this.
I throw it.
When I pick it up, it's back in that spot up here.
It doesn't automatically go to, like, there.
I gotta say, I didn't even pay attention, but that is something that is specifically designed to be that way.
And I really appreciate that.
That is actually such a small thing, but it's such a big thing at the same time.
Very happy about that.
Hey, you there.
Boink!
It's actually...
Like, if there's a stack of enemies, this is legitimately the best way to kill them in the beginning.
And not, like, with your spells, because sometimes their corpses block the other enemies.
And you can't hit them.
The layout of this hemisphere is very annoying.
I feel like every path is blocked to me.
Okay, there was a wand somewhere over here that I want to grab.
Concentrated mana, I'll take that.
A bunch of sawblades.
Chainsaws.
Okay, it's not fast, so I can't really saw people.
But that's gonna be nice for later when I have to make something speedy.
Let's go up here now.
Oh wait, I have money for this.
I'm gonna buy that barrier now.
You know what?
I also have to consider this.
Okay, so let's say I get to a holy mountain.
And I don't have any obvious safe and quick way to dispatch of Zed.
I may just have to accept that I'm not gonna kill him.
And just collapse the mountain.
Because I always have the chance of getting a spot later on that will allow me to change the wand, right?
So maybe I just have to do that.
Buy that.
And then we kill this dude.
With...
He's burning.
I'm just gonna leave him burn.
Please die.
I can help him out a bit.
Oh my god, I just spawned a bunch.
Oh, what have I done?
What have I done?
It's terrible.
Wait.
There we go.
Come here.
Damn it.
I'm gonna tablet him.
You wanna, you wanna tablet?
There you go.
Tablet for you.
Water.
Water, water, water, water, water.
I'm gonna tablet.
Oh, watch this, watch this, watch this.
Oh no, he sees me.
Hello, come down here, come down here.
Yes, come down.
Yes, and watch.
Hey, sir.
Boink.
400 damage, baby.
Now beat that in the hemisphere.
That is wild.
Thank you.
Do you wanna buy anything else?
Maybe the cloud, actually.
Like, it does an electrical charge, right?
Thunder cloud.
Creates a stormy cloud.
So I guess that's the same type of stormy cloud that follows you around when you get hit by the projectiles of those guys.
I forget the names of them.
What is their name, anyway?
Where are you?
I'm kind of curious what they're called.
Those little assholes.
What is this guy called?
Stivari?
Stivari.
Suomo Hauki.
What's that?
Oh, Colmi Silma.
Uh, where's this guy?
There.
Merkienen.
Merkienen?
Okay.
Murica.
What's going on here?
Another sand pillar.
Oh, but with some XP down there.
Um, I may have to blow the shit up.
You know how it is.
And in fact, I'm gonna go all in.
Look at that.
Lovely stuff.
Oh, but the sand is burying it, right?
Oh no, we're fine.
Yeah.
Okay.
I don't know what just happened.
But, uh, all right.
That's fair.
All right.
Cool.
Very nice.
Unbelievable.
Wow.
But look at that.
We get a wand.
So that's nice.
That's a little bit of a...
Oh, and a chest.
Oh, I'm rich!
Oh my god, the game's like, I'm so sorry about that.
Here, have a, have a little bit of a consolation prize.
And you know what?
I take that prize any day.
That's a good prize.
660 money, baby, from that.
And what's this?
Flamox...
Yeah, see, I don't want flamoxium.
Although I do want the flask.
So I'll take that.
So that's nice.
Now, game, if you want to please me right now, give me plasma cutter.
I'll take it.
I will take that.
I do actually have an uncanny knack for predicting what's in a wand.
And I'll, and I'll, I'll prove it to you.
The next one will be fine.
I will have a very high chance of predicting what's in it.
You don't believe me, I see that, but trust me.
I have a sixth sense.
In fact, I know when things happen before they happen.
Except that thing that happened just before.
That one came out of the blue, I gotta be honest.
Why were you moving?
This barrel just moved by itself.
Get away.
You know what I really want?
I want...
Dude, if I have...
If I have...
What's it called?
Telekinetic kick.
If I have that perk, I think I could easily kill Zed.
Because there's a lot of force when you kick things around.
And if I bring a tablet, and instead of throwing it, I telekinetic kick it, it lights out for him.
Lights out, baby.
But I guess you would have to have that perk first, so that's another thing.
Now show me some HP.
I feel like I haven't seen much HP.
I mean, I found one before, but then I died immediately after, so that was kind of a bummer.
By the way, I think I realized what happened before.
I threw the little explosive box, right?
I blew the bomb, and for some reason, I don't think the box exploded yet.
Maybe it was burning.
So when I arrived, the box exploded, and it did 125 damage, because that's how much damage they do.
And then it was lights out.
That was the end of me.
Okay, more bombs, I'll take it.
So what I learned from that is those boxes suck, except when you want to use them against the set.
Oh, okay, not bad, not bad.
Somehow I haven't lost a single point of HP.
Uh-oh, my god, look at him.
He's ruining the entire level.
How dare you?
Turn it all into water.
Oh, that was close.
I got hit.
The no-hit run is over.
Ah, dammit, it was a close one.
I almost had it, guys.
Water the portal?
Let's go up here.
Look at him, he's just having a little bath.
I need to fill my water bottle.
What if I put flammoxium on you?
Would you enjoy that very much?
Are you confused?
I didn't even hit him, I think.
Oi!
You know what?
I feel like I'm gonna get high.
Let's get high, then.
When I find, uh, fungals, I'm gonna get high.
That's the plan.
Oh, yeah, we're getting high.
I feel... You know how I said I could predict the future?
I feel like I see, uh, I see a good thing in the future.
And not a bad thing.
Mmm, fire bolts.
No.
Keep it.
Oh, I need to go...
What is up with all this toxic shit?
There's so, like I said, so much of it.
Compared to usual.
Oh, no.
I'm toxic!
Okay, I'm fine.
Hey, come here.
That would be the perfect throw, though, to be honest.
Oh, my god!
If I die here, I'm actually gonna scream like a little child.
I'm gonna throw a tantrum.
Once... You know what?
I'll take that.
I will take it.
Nice.
Actually, give me the money.
Give me something good.
Okay.
I was about to predict what was in there.
I was about to say, uh, cloud with, uh, water.
But yeah, it was too fast.
But you can see I was right, so...
I may take it.
We have so much fucking toxic.
Guys, it's over.
I'm gonna die here for sure.
We're leaving.
Yeah, we're leaving.
We're out of here.
Sayonara!
Show me what's good.
Dammit.
Nothing's good.
What's that?
You're getting two random perks?
Yes!
Protectile slower?
Slower?
Explosion immunity?
You know what?
Thank you.
I appreciate that, my friend.
I appreciate that.
Now, to find a good one.
Point one eight.
Point three eight.
Oh, but spells per cast is two.
What do I have now?
This one is...
Ah, it's shuffle, never mind.
Never mind.
Maybe I'll take...
Oh, it's only two slots.
I guess this one is actually decent.
It's like very mid, I guess.
The casted lay is quite high.
I mean, this one ain't bad.
Okay, so it's huge two spells per cast, so what?
It's actually okay.
Take it.
Replace...
That one.
Hold on, before I take it, let's put these up here.
Let's put all the spells up here first.
Can I buy this?
Acid ball.
Is that even something I would like to have?
I really don't think so.
Wait, where does this flammable gas come from?
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, no.
Oh, it slows my projectiles too.
Ah, that's fine.
That's fine.
That's actually okay.
I don't mind.
I can deal with that.
Now, with this one...
That's actually not bad.
That's a good start.
Good start.
But we could do with more, so maybe I'll take this one.
Throw these on here.
Actually, remove this.
It's better.
Not bad.
What if I do this?
Actually kind of sick, because...
So, it reduces cast delay, right?
And recharge time.
And this is only going to affect one of these.
This one.
Because it's going to run through normally.
And then when it reaches this one, it's going to affect only one more, which is that one.
But what if I did...
Dude.
I just had an idea.
What if we put a worthless spell in there?
Like, okay, so let's say I had a drill.
Just let heavy spread affect the drill, and it's going to be like, I don't care.
But it's still going to have an effect on the rest.
Right?
Like, it's the same here.
Actually, no, it's not the same, because this one will affect two of them, I guess.
This one will only affect...
Yeah, I guess two of them as well.
Why do that?
I mean, that's not bad.
I just don't like it very much, that's all.
That's cool.
Although...
Hold on a second.
Hey, what the hell?
That's really good.
Hell yeah, now we're talking.
Oh, that's sweet.
Lovely.
Okay, so now we make bombs, we make shielding, and we make rain clouds.
How about them apples?
In fact, I think I love them apples.
They're my favorite.
You know what, I'm going to buy this just to have one more.
I'm that much of a fat cat.
No.
There we go.
There we go, fill it up.
Oh, that's lovely, that's lovely.
And then we change this one back.
And now we're ready to rock and roll, baby.
Let me sort this a bit.
Hold on.
We don't have any methods of, yeah, see, in this situation, we can't do much.
We actually cannot kill Zed, because we can't anger Zed.
So we can leave.
It is what it is.
Sometimes that happens.
What's this?
Actually, yo.
Oh, actually, no, no, nevermind.
It's actually pretty good.
If this wasn't shuffled, this would be insane.
No.
Just the shuffle is kind of bad.
The shuffle kind of sucks.
Dude, explosion immunity is sick.
That is that, if I had seen that, I would have just taken it.
So that is lovely.
That is actually pretty cool.
You.
Give me that money.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Let's try not to die to something stupid.
This time.
Oh, look at this.
Protectile slowing down.
Ah.
Somehow this motherfucker still hits me.
Oh, there's a heart there.
Muchas gracias.
I should use my rain cloud.
Hold on.
I'm gonna do it over here.
Let's see it again.
Amazing.
Dude, that is a thick wand.
Look at that.
That is a wide wand.
Huh?
Okay, let's move on.
What's up, man?
Wow.
Found the portal already.
That was a quick one.
But I'm not...
Oh, he has a wand.
Emergency stations.
Okay, he shoots that shit.
That's okay.
That's not too bad, I guess.
That's fine.
In fact, that shit...
Doug, I saw that.
Oh, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude.
Oh, that's legit.
The dig is real.
Love the dig.
Holy shit.
Yo, I've been sleeping on that, dick.
Hey!
How much does it do in damage?
Oh, I hate that it slows down near me, though.
Oh, we're getting rich.
It's rich!
Look at this!
Oh!
That's amazing.
That pleases me so much.
Show me secrets.
Secrets, secrets.
Secrets, secrets, secrets, secrets.
Why is everything shaking?
We flood the entire level.
Wow, how did you not die?
You know what?
I think the last time I had this perk, with the projectile slower field, that is the run where I got really far.
So I feel like, and I'm not superstitious or anything, but this may be the one.
Just saying.
You know?
Maybe that is the reason why I got so far, is I had that.
Think about it.
Have you thought about it?
Okay.
When you've thought about it, I want you to think about your dad.
What's your dad like?
Would love to meet that dad.
Was that not gold?
I've been bamboozled.
Oh, it does dig through gray rock, but it's like very bad.
What's up, fool?
Oh.
Okay, there's stuff up there.
That's mysterious looking.
You know what?
I'm lazy.
I'm going to rain cloud this shit.
Boing!
Get rid of all the toxic!
And nothing.
Oh, actually.
Okay, my plan for this...
coal pit.
I will not leave unless I have 2000 buckies in my pockies.
Because...
And it's only because I died so unfairly the other time when I had that much money.
And I want to be able to get back into that mental state of mind.
Where I felt amazing having that amount of buckies.
So that's the plan.
We're going to be digging.
And only because the dig is real.
Don't forget that.
Like, I'm only doing this because we actually have a real one.
The energy orb is something else.
What's that?
Ambrosia!
That was close.
That beam almost broke the ambrosia.
Should I be using the energy orb to kill people too?
Maybe.
Hold on.
Uh, best way to get in here would probably be to...
I think I hear an Ukuskivi.
I'm scared, guys.
Got it!
You hear it?
There's an Ukuskivi somewhere.
Why is that beam traveling on its own?
It has become a worm.
Dude, how is this energy orb digging better than actual digging spells?
Blowing my mind.
Oh, we're slowly accruing the buckies.
Actually, we're doing it quite fast.
Go to hell.
All a y'all.
There's a wand.
Personal fireball thrower.
I had this once and it was actually kind of good.
I remember using it with a glowing lance.
But I'm not gonna take it.
But it is something to consider.
It's like super good against...
Dude.
I was about to say it's super good against strong enemies.
Because it just keeps shooting fireballs.
It would actually be kind of cool to try that on a boss.
Right?
Assuming you can hit them with it.
Because if you can just hit them with something and just fuck off and let pandemonium happen on its own.
That would be a great way to play it safely.
Uh, let me dig up here.
I think I love this projectile repulsion field.
It's like a safety bubble.
It's like...
it's so nice.
Like a little personal space.
Get out of here.
Oh god.
Am I poisoned?
What's happening?
I was just toxic sludge.
1300 buckaroos.
Uh-oh.
He has a wand.
Wait, circle of...
Wait a minute.
Shielding.
Where are you, fucker?
Oh, I just know he's going to kill me.
He's going to have some bullshit on that wand.
And it's just going to murder me.
I can feel it, guys.
Oh, shit.
Hey, fuck it.
Fuck it.
Come here.
Oh, he bleeds teleportation.
Where is he?
Where did you go?
Yo, what?
That's pretty cool.
I don't need it, though.
But nice.
Man, that was just hiding in plain sight, almost.
There you are, fucker.
Hey!
Gotcha!
Hey there.
Now that I like.
I may just steal that from you, sir.
Maybe I'll replace this one.
I'm not that big a fan of the rain cloud.
You know?
But it's like, okay.
Let's see how it does.
It shoots those like it said it would.
Not much of a surprise there, I guess.
Buckies!
Whoa!
Bomber guy.
Oh yeah, I'm immune to explosions, for fuck's sake.
I kind of forgot about that.
That's awesome.
Oh, not you.
Go away.
Okay, not bad, not bad.
That was smooth.
Well done, Oliver.
And here we have our exit.
1600 golds.
To our name.
Oh!
I tried that wand already.
I mean, I switched it there.
Okay, another wand.
That's exciting.
I will check it out.
Look at me.
Playing worms.
The digger!
Oh no.
Hold up, hold up, hold up, hold up a second.
Let's take it easy.
He took it.
This motherfucker.
Are you for real?
They both have a wand.
Hold on.
I have a heart.
Oh, there's a heart.
Thank you.
This is getting a little scary.
I can't lie guys.
Oh nice, nice, nice.
What do you have on the wand?
Oh, it's the digger wand.
This digger wand.
This is, this is, this is a... Okay, so he's not doing anything really.
So basically I need to kill him.
Do I take damage every time?
What's this?
Oh, wait, always, always cast rock.
Oh, yo, that's infinite.
Pretty much.
Right?
He's through more than three.
Hold on.
I need to think.
Like rocks?
Did I just hit myself?
What just happened?
Oh my god, this is not good.
Please die.
Okay, I'm not taking damage.
There we go.
Get out of here, you asshole.
Now the question is, what do I replace?
Maybe that one.
It's shuffle anyway.
It sucks.
I think that's it.
We go.
Hold on.
We don't have 2000 buckaroos.
1942 is the amount we have right now.
I'm not leaving without the buggies.
I tell you that.
1959?
1982?
1991?
That's one year off from my birthday.
There we go.
2008.
A great year that everyone loves.
Let's go.
Cool.
Let's heal up.
Interesting.
What the fuck is that?
Giga black hole.
I never tried that, I don't think.
We got to try that.
What's this?
Oil blood?
You bleed flammable oil, but are immune to fire.
Someone said, actually, this one wasn't too bad.
It does make me slippery a lot.
But being immune to fire and explosion immunity together, now that is a proposition that's hard to resist, isn't it?
I'm doing it.
I'm going with it.
Of course.
And now I'm going to try this.
The Giga black hole.
A growing orb of negative energy that destroys everything in its reach.
Sweet.
So what, this is just going to be a bigger black hole?
I mean, not that I'm complaining, I'm just asking the question.
Let's be careful not to anger anybody now.
I don't know what this is capable of.
I don't know how big this is going to be, actually.
Let's have some safety precautions here.
I would love to have... Oh, but hold on.
I was thinking, so when I saw this wand always casts rock, I was thinking, yo, that would be sick if I had homing.
But it's always going to cast that first.
So even if I put homing on this, it's not actually going to home anywhere.
So what it needs is to have the perk that gives me homing for that to even make any sense.
That's what I'm seeing here.
And we have digging bolts.
That could be kind of exciting.
Maybe I wait with... I'm going to wait with trying this until we get out of this place, because I don't want to anger said immediately here.
Oh, I could try this stuff.
Is that a...
Ooh, hold on a second.
That would be a way, maybe, if I can get through his damn shield.
What's that?
Personal gravity field.
Hold on a second.
If I'm immune to fire...
Wait a second now, guys.
Wait a second.
Hold on now.
Wait a minute.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
How does that work?
What's this?
Toxic mist?
Ew.
Well, yeah, let's try this.
Wait a minute.
Huh?
It is casting it.
Wait, does it need to be the same?
Requires two protectile spells.
Oh, maybe it doesn't... maybe I can't do it with a trigger.
Is that it?
Hold on.
Let me try these two.
They are considered projectiles.
Oh, yeah, I'm definitely producing fire.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's working, I think.
Why doesn't this... It is being applied.
This should shoot both of these at the...
Oh, you know what?
I need this.
I need to spread them out.
Otherwise, the arc is not really going to be useful.
But hold on, we need to... Where's that spell there?
There we go, look.
There it is.
Look at that.
Hey, that's cool.
That's cool, man.
That's actually pretty cool.
Dude, if I keep this one here, it's always going to...
Oh.
Wait, what?
Oh, I guess the arc only lasts as long as the actual projectile lasts.
I was thinking I could have my digging bolt, which is like melee range, and shoot a long range, and it will create an arc always between me and my projectile, sort of like a grappling hook that you shoot.
You know what I mean?
Like on a rope, except the fiery rope.
But this one is actually lasting very short, so that's why the arc isn't there to see.
I understand.
Yeah, pretty cool.
I mean, that's pretty dope.
I think we can do some stuff with that, probably.
This one is not doing, of course, what we expect, because reasons.
What if I do this?
Is that actually shooting three?
No, wait.
I guess.
Okay, so the trigger ones are a little special, aren't they?
Like it's kind of hard to understand what's happening with those sometimes.
But yeah, that's cool.
I want to keep this because we now are immune to fire.
We can, in fact, how about we do this?
I forgot about that one.
Wait a minute now.
I think I like it.
I think I like that.
Now, can we do some digging?
Oh shit, that always shoots a rock.
I forgot.
This one?
How about two of them?
That's what I'm talking about.
How about this one, though?
What if we add more?
Okay, that's not as exciting, I gotta admit.
That's very exciting.
That makes me excited.
Even more exciting!
Look at that!
Holy shit!
That's it!
That's the digger!
That is big dig and it's right there!
Fantastic!
Okay, now do I want any of these other...
Oh wait, teleport!
Of course I want that!
The fuck?
No, not on that one.
Oh, but I want to... Okay, you know what?
I'm gonna try this now.
I want to try it now.
Let's... Okay, I'm gonna shoot it this way.
Hopefully it's not gonna... Oh, please don't.
Okay, if shit hits the fan, I leave this place.
I'm out of here.
I'm gonna teleport my way.
In fact, I'm gonna dig down and teleport out if... Hold on, no, I'm not, because then I anger the guy.
I'm an idiot.
I'm gonna go this way and then if something happens, I go down.
That's the plan.
Go!
Wait, what?
Oh no.
What?!
Okay, that's... Oh no.
Oh no.
Oh no!
No, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no!
Come on.
Yep.
Eat it, eat it, eat it, eat it.
We're leaving!
We are leaving!
Go!
Eat it up!
We are out of here, baby!
Unless, hold on, can I maybe kill him with this?
It does throw stuff around.
Oh, dude, dude, I have an idea.
This is my backup plan.
Hey, sir, you like black holes, right?
That's something you enjoy, I know it is.
Oh, shit.
Oh, look.
Yeah!
Look at his spells!
Oh, wait, he's not dead.
Sir?
I used them all.
I'm trying this now.
Oh, I don't know about that one.
Oh, I don't know about this, guys.
I can't get out.
Okay, okay.
It's over, I think.
How do I kill him?
Oh, no.
Wait, I've teleported.
Wait, what?
I fucked up, guys!
It's over, I'm dead!
It's over, it's over, it's over, I can't teleport.
Fuck, hell, are you actually kidding me, man?
That was such a good run, man.
Ruined by fucking Sid again.
I swear to god, I fucking hate that guy so much!
Pissing me off, man.
Now my game crashed.
Oh, that's fucking lovely.
Ugh!
It's every- oh, you know what?
I'm actually just gonna restart then, because there's probably a- oh, new game.
Okay.
There's no restore from backup, it seems.
Whatever.
Well, now I have chaotic polymorphine on me, which is something every man needs, of course, when you start a game.
Very lovely stuff.
You die.
I... fucking hell, man.
Blow it up.
I hate that guy so much, it's insane.
I can't tell you how much I fucking despise that person.
I can't even get through there.
Unless I use this, but I don't want to kick it all the way over there.
Too much work.
You there.
There's a wand, that's something.
Now, if you can give me a normal black hole in that, I would be eternally grateful.
You gonna throw me a bone game?
Eh?
Nah, you know what?
I need to, uh, wait.
Okay, that's what I'm talking about.
That's a good wand.
That's nice.
Uh-oh, can't get through there, but I... Yes, I can.
There we go.
It's a bit risky, uh, surface here.
For a very shitty wand, too.
That's odd.
Ah, man.
I had such good perks, man.
All lost because of that same fucker again.
Fuck.
I have no water.
Guess I'm burning alive.
I don't even care.
Don't even care.
Take me.
Fuck.
Let's go again.
Okay, I still have shitty bombs.
Oh my god.
What is it with my chance here?
Like, come on.
Okay.
This time, this is, this is the run, guys.
This is the run where I will get the chance to have a chance to maybe become powerful enough to get another shot at perhaps killing a boss down the line, which could reveal something about the world.
That's what I'm hoping for.
So, but all those things need to be going right for me from the get-go.
And I am, you know, a polymorph me.
Take out the fire with that.
Come on.
Switch me back, please.
Okay, let's go.
Oh, fire is coming down now, so I can't go.
I'm on fire.
I am toxic.
Okay.
This is a very bad start.
This is terrible.
Absolutely terrible start.
Let's go up here again.
I am starting to hate the hemisphere.
Hatersphere is the new word for this place.
How's that?
It's whiskey.
Oh, that's gonna release fire.
Yep.
I don't care.
Electricity and fire?
Damn, that, this game wants me dead, bro.
They really don't want me to live in here.
I need some water.
And I need to get rid of this polymorphine that's in my goddamn flask.
Get it out of here.
All of it.
Nice.
I'm starting to reach the point where I feel like I should maybe just immediately go for the holy mountain.
Just to see if there's any perks that are worth it.
Otherwise, just restart.
Is that the fucking meta?
I don't understand.
Like, it's insane.
Like,
you spend so much time up here, right?
It's just...
And then fucking setup comes out of nowhere and it's just like...
But I guess now I know what a giga black hole does.
That's the silver lining on all this.
At least I know that now.
Silly me assumed a giga black hole was a black hole, but...
Giga, you know?
How silly of me.
Oh, he's gonna have a bath and you won't enjoy it.
That's right, bitch!
Okay, go this way.
Oh, no!
There's two of them!
What the fuck, man?
What is this?
This is a brutal hemisphere.
I think we're just dipping out immediately.
Yeah, fuck this.
Let's go.
We have 200-something gold.
We can buy a couple spells and shit.
It's not the worst.
Let's see what we have.
Well, don't have money for that.
A black hole and we have money for it.
That's not bad.
Let's see what the perks are.
Is that what I think it is?
It is not.
It is a pinpointer.
Kills to me.
I don't think I'm like that.
I think I need to use my money here on some spells if I want to survive.
Like, this is nice, but it's not like immediately... Oh, you know what?
Can we kill set in here with whatever we got?
Hmm.
I mean, okay.
I think I could do... I could black hole my way.
Let's say I black hole my way out here, right?
I make a black hole here and as soon as I do it, I leave.
I go out here and I find this big open spot to fight him and I learn how to actually kill this motherfucker with my wand.
Like, it's got to be possible to just straight up murder this guy with enough skill.
And I plan to attain that skill because I am so tired of him.
I want to be able to kill him no matter what happens.
But he does have that shield, right?
We need something against that.
Is that... Hold on.
Is that fireball orbit?
I think it is.
That could maybe be something we can use.
Oh, but I don't even have money to buy this one.
And this is with the...
Oh, hold on.
If I buy this, I could put fireball orbit on...
Oh, but that probably cost a lot of mana to cast, right?
And all I have is shuffle ones, the ones that aren't shit.
But hold on, this is not a shuffle one.
So I could use this, I guess.
Buy it.
Fireball orbit.
Okay, okay, okay.
I mean, let's test it.
Let's see how good this is against...
Against set here.
It cast three spells as well.
So that's interesting.
Why not?
Let's see here.
I mean, that's pretty dope, right?
If that doesn't kill him.
I mean, oh, it does have a long recharge though.
That sucks ass.
Hold on, it costs 40 mana.
Maybe it's better up here.
I think it is.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're gonna go with that.
And then maybe, if he comes around like this... Okay, if we could learn to kill him with bombs, that would be sick.
If I just throw some bombs down here, you know?
They're gonna blow around this place.
And bombs do like to 125.
That's actually a lot.
That could be a strategy.
So this one does 1.5 recharge.
That's too much.
Let's put it on...
No, actually it's okay.
It's okay.
Yeah.
And your spells fly faster.
No, I think I'm gonna get a re-roll.
All right, let's just try and mess with this guy.
Let's see how mad he gets.
I'm gonna make him mad over here, so I have an escape at least.
Oh, he's so mad now.
He's so mad.
Look at him.
He's gonna come in here and be so mad.
Hey, fuck it.
In fact, when he comes down here, I'm gonna bomb him first, just to see how that goes.
Come on.
That's right.
No.
Okay, that's fine.
That's for you.
Okay, that did some damage.
Okay, that did some damage to me.
Oh, he blew up the bomb mid-air.
Okay, I see.
Okay, yeah.
All right, that's cool.
Let's go again.
We have to find a way to deal with him.
Unless... Hold on.
New strategy.
What if we just say, fuck it, we don't deal with them in the first one?
I mean, technically all we need in reality is to have a single holy mountain where we can change our wants.
I mean, that's why I'm doing all this, right?
So let's say I simply wait.
I simply wait until I know I can kill him, like easily.
And then I make that holy mountain my hub or whatever, my main base.
You know?
That could be a strategy.
We don't necessarily have to make the first one one of the bases.
You know what I mean?
So I think it's a good idea.
Actually, how about we do that?
That sounds not bad.
Also, I'm gonna blow this up.
Give me the wand.
All right, lots of fire.
Yeah, that's the new strategy.
Fuck making the first holy mountain clean, I've said.
We're gonna do it on the next ones.
Because chances are you're not gonna find anything good to deal with them anyway so early, right?
That's what I'm thinking now.
What's that?
Coal pouch?
How about no?
The place I'm going?
The next area?
There's plenty of coal.
I don't need a pouch for that.
Oh my god.
Okay, we're getting high immediately.
Oh yeah, oh yeah, baby.
We are getting high as fuck.
That's the only way to cope with this situation.
Everybody knows it.
Come on.
Oh, weird fungus.
Echo and shifting in colors.
I need to remember what exactly does that mean.
Oh, there's a wand.
A wand for me.
Lots of fire bolts.
Yeah, sure.
Wait.
Wait a second.
What was transformed here?
Hold on.
Wait a second.
No.
Wait a minute.
What was transformed here?
Hold on a second.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No.
Water has become weird fungus.
You know what that means, right?
We're getting high, bitch.
Oh, we're getting high.
This is Nirvana.
Let's fucking go.
Oh yeah.
Eat it all up, boy.
Oh yeah, this is a moment.
Oh, we're getting so fucking high.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, puke it out, boy.
Puke, puke, puke.
Oh wait, I can only get so satiated though.
Oh, I'm really high right now.
Holy shit.
Wait, come on.
Why is nothing happening?
Give me another message.
Oh my god.
700 seconds of highness.
Oh, get ready.
This is nuts.
Oh, hmm.
I saw the eyes, but that's about it.
What the hell?
Is there like an internal cooldown on this?
Probably actually.
Maybe I just need to wait a bit.
Oh, I didn't even see you there, Hamish, because I'm high as fuck.
Oh, yeah.
In fact, I can't even fucking walk without tripping over myself.
What's up, my friend?
What is that?
Can I eat that?
No, that's vomit.
You don't want to eat vomit.
Vomit is real bad.
That's a chest.
Nope.
It's a cannon, I think.
Oh my god.
Look how pretty.
I will kill you.
I will murder you.
Why do I feel like I'm immune to damage?
No, this is hurting me.
I'm not hurt by this.
Oh, wait a minute.
I don't have any water.
It's all fungus.
Oh, shit.
What's that?
It's oil.
What did I pick up?
Concentrated mana.
You know, that is my new water.
That will function as water.
Nothing can stop me now.
Oh, yeah.
Look at all these fucking aliens.
Oh, no.
Oops.
Well, that was a little crazy.
I mean, fucking water.
It's a weird fungus.
I mean, okay.
Sure, dude.
Sure.
That was kind of crazy.
Okay.
Very hard to play as well when you're that high, I gotta tell you.
Like, you can't even see what the hell is going on, you know?
You can't even discern what the different liquids are.
Unstable teleportation.
You know what?
I feel like drinking that.
Yeah.
I feel unstable.
We're doing it.
Because why not?
Dude, I just had an idea.
I've solved all my issues.
I've solved all of my issues.
I know what to do.
And the answer?
No.
The answer?
Teleportation.
And a bit of luck.
That's all I'm saying.
If you'll see soon enough what I have in mind.
I shall not reveal the master plan yet because it's so genius.
It shall be a surprise.
What's happening?
What the fuck is that?
What?
Say what now?
Little hammers.
Volcanic rock.
Okay.
Now, that thing can fuck right off.
But I'm taking it with me.
It's more safe in my hands than it is out there in the wild.
You know?
Oh, dude.
That's my answer.
Set, you're dead.
Set, you're fucking dead now.
I got you motherfucker.
All I need is three bottles of water.
Okay?
That's all I need.
Actually, maybe more.
I need a water spell.
Water spell.
Water.
Is that whiskey?
There's definitely whiskey there.
How do I get in there?
Hold on a second.
Why is it all toxic too?
I don't like that.
I'm gonna bomb it.
Bombing.
Shit.
I guess I'll do it from up here.
That works.
Hell yeah, we're back.
Oh, that's very annoying.
Hold on, I have swamp.
Ouch!
Okay, well, that's actually pretty dope.
I like it, I like it.
That means cave.
It's cave time.
Cave time.
We can go caving now.
Swamp it up.
Swamp that ass.
And we got a wand.
Give me something delicious now, game.
I'll take it.
That's very delicious.
I won't say it's wonderful, but it's definitely up there in taste.
I enjoy that one.
Let's get rid of all this.
Dude, as soon as I see fungus, I'm gonna eat it.
As soon as I spot that fungus, I will consume.
Like there's no tomorrow.
I am not a feared of the fungus anymore.
In fact, I embrace the fungus.
I welcome it into my life.
Oh, let's get some water.
Okay.
Don't spray on me.
All right, that's good enough.
Come here.
Oh, he's a sheep.
Oh, hold on.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh, shit.
No fucking way.
That's scary.
I don't want to be this thing.
So what we have here is chaotic polymorphine and
ambrosia.
Oh, look, look at this.
This guy's puking.
I don't want to shoot him because I'm going to release him.
You did, son.
Yeah, you did.
Oh, there's all kinds of crap in that.
Look at all that.
Thank you.
Unstable.
Yeah, I need that.
You know what?
Oh, man.
I need all of this.
Hmm.
Well, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait a second.
I'm just realizing maybe my idea is not as great as I thought it would be.
This may actually be really bad.
Hmm.
Yeah.
Ah, hold on.
Nah, it's bad.
That's a, I have a, the idea I had is terrible.
I just realized it's a terrible idea.
Fuck.
But if I can find a rain spell, I'm good.
Rain spell and we're home free.
I'm looking for rain spell.
Rain, rain, rain, rain.
Too much fire, man.
What happened here?
Damn, son.
What's that?
Chaotic polymorphine.
Look at this again.
It's, it's so often.
Like that tile is present.
Burn or dissolve, I guess.
Wow.
That frog just murdered me.
Really kicked my ass there.
I got outplayed.
Acid potion?
Actually,
why don't we try that?
I'm going to get rid of this.
Off you go.
I want acid.
Maybe Zed likes acid.
Acid, acid.
He likes a bit of acid in his face.
What's that?
Cocktail.
Hold on a second.
Maybe I want that instead.
Liquid fire and oil.
Oh, that's, that's fucked up.
This motherfucker broke my water bottle.
I'm dead.
I'm Brozier.
I block, I block, I block, I don't block.
I'm dead.
Yeah, man.
Ah, fuck.
You know what?
That's it, man.
Four and a half hours of nothing.
Jesus.
I'm not getting anywhere in this game, guys.
It's actually a disaster.
It's a massive disaster.
Oh, goddamn it.
I'm losing patience to play patiently.
And that's fighting me in the ass.
You know?
Like, it's kind of insane.
It takes like, what is it?
So at least for me, I think it takes me, let's say, three to four hours of a good run.
Maybe get to a place where I can try new stuff.
You know what I mean?
Or like, explore new areas.
But just getting to that point is actually insanely difficult.
So yeah, it's getting a little difficult here, guys.
I'm not gonna lie.
How you guys doing?
Very sad day today.
I mean, it was still fun, but I would just really love to explore the new areas I found, you know?
And I'm just... the game is basically gatekeeping those areas until you check off a certain amount of lock rules, I guess, for getting the right perks, getting the right spells, or at least... I mean, obviously, I know there's those things that I miss.
You know, there's combinations of spells that I haven't tried yet that could be amazing and all that.
But like, a lot of things need to go right, and you need to play really well to even get another shot at getting some progress.
You know what I mean?
It's very difficult.
It's similar to Rainworld in that sense.
Yeah, I guess so, but I would say...
Okay, I would still say Rainworld is a harder game.
Because that game is insane, okay?
Like, in this game, for example, if you want to beat the game, sure.
I mean, I can probably go down and beat the game.
If I, you know, play patiently and... like, I've had many opportunities, I think, to beat the game, other than the first time.
I mean, I'm just saying that, of course.
I don't know if I had.
Maybe I couldn't have done it.
Who knows?
That's always the big if, right?
But in Rainworld, it's... at least you have, like, save points, basically.
That is the big difference.
Whereas here, it truly is.
I mean, it is a rogue-like.
But a rogue-like...
where a lot of the secret stuff and all that is, like, hidden very deep in a run.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, I mean, things are much less RNG-based, if you truly know the game well, for what it's worth.
Yeah, exactly, exactly.
Like, just the fact that I learned how to...
or even learned of the idea that you could leave a holy mountain and then come back and change my ones later is, like, an amazing knowledge to have, right?
And who knows?
Maybe there's something else on that level of that knowledge out there that would change everything.
Yeah.
It's hard, man.
But I'm gonna keep trying.
At some point, I'm gonna get the right combination of perks and I'm not gonna suck.
You know, like, a combination of me being in the moment, you know, and really fucking owning.
And with good perks and all some good spells and stuff like that, then it's gonna be crazy.
But I can easily imagine that if you're good enough, you could technically always do it, you know?
Like, I still haven't tried my whole idea of going straight to the snowy depths and looking for some sick ones or something like that.
Sounds difficult, though, you know, with all the enemies there and you don't have a lot of fire power, but it would be something to try, I guess.
Yeah.
Your last idea of just ignoring the first holy mountains?
Yeah, exactly.
I think... So the way I'm gonna approach this now, from now on, is if I find something super amazing that I know I can use to kill him,
then I'll do it, right?
But if I don't, then I'm just gonna be like, okay, fine.
That's okay.
I collapse the holy mountain, I move on, and then I just do it on the next one.
I basically...
So, and the chances of me getting something at some point that will allow one of the holy mountains to be intact is pretty high, right?
So that has to be the strategy from now on.
Yeah.
It's definitely the most consistent way of doing it.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
I did actually learn some stuff today, of course, like with the Giga Black Hole and also some other stuff, I think, that I experimented with.
Oh, yeah, I figured out some ways to kill... to kill Zed too, right?
Everyone was spamming RIP when you're about to cast Giga Black Hole.
I love that.
That's funny.
So what I imagined would happen, so it read Giga Black Hole.
I thought, okay, you know what?
It's exactly the same as the other Black Hole.
It's just much larger in radius.
But I didn't think it would be bigger than the size of the room large.
So I thought if I shot it left, it would just go along the room and not destroy any brickwork, you know?
Like at maximum, it's going to be the size of the room, I thought, and not more.
And it's gonna continue on.
So yeah.
Oh, the digging with energy orb is a big one.
Holy shit, you're right.
How can I not be interested in Giga Black Holes, though?
That is Giga interesting.
If you see something called a Giga Black Hole in a video game, it's pretty much a must that you gotta check it out.
It sounds too interesting, right?
But I guess I should have tried it outside of the Holy Mountain.
That was my mistake.
I considered doing it outside of the Holy Mountain too, and then I didn't.
Because I was like, ah, it's gotta be like the normal Black Hole, right?
Nope, it's not.
So many times we've screamed at the screen when you've thrown out energy orbs away.
Oh, I wonder how many times I've had that thing, man.
And the worst part is, I think I've used it before to dig.
I just didn't remember.
Because I feel like I have a memory of digging with that at some point.
Well, that's not crazy.
Okuskivi chest death is a smoking duck.
What does that mean?
Hold on.
Oh, classic.
It's a classic.
Oh, I see.
I see.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm pretty sure my first gig of Black Hole killed me.
You know what?
I'm glad to know I'm not the only one dying in these ways, you know?
But I think slowly I'm building up my repertoire of knowledge.
And at some point I'll be unstoppable.
No, that's today.
Oh, yeah, right.
I have to increase the counter.
Oh, but at this point it doesn't matter, I guess.
But I think we're at like 87 or something.
88, maybe even.
Maybe you guys know.
Definitely almost 90.
The best players have month-long streaks of zero deaths in this game?
Doesn't surprise me.
I mean, people do crazy shit in video games.
Not really a big surprise.
Or like doing no hit runs in Rainworld sounds fucking insane.
And people do it, you know?
Or like beating all of the Souls game one after another without getting hit.
That's been done and that blows my mind.
I mean, I'm not surprised.
People are insane.
There's some real gamers out there.
You used it to dig snow and only snow.
Oh, did I?
Oh, I remember that now, actually.
I think.
Yeah.
I remember I had some kind of spell to dig snow.
And it was a big one.
That must have been it.
The knighted discord has an ukuskimi death counter.
That's amazing.
I love that the community is so self-aware about it.
Your chicken rice with bernay sauce was very good, was it?
Did you put a picture on the discord?
There's a food channel, you know?
You're obligated to put your food pictures there.
But that's good, man.
I'm glad it came out good.
If you find out the community way of killing Steve in the wrap-up stream, then you will be so disappointed.
The community way, huh?
Hold on, let me think.
What would that be?
Obviously, don't tell me.
I'm trying to think.
If I will be disappointed, it's got to be something so stupid.
It's got to be something so dumb.
What could it be?
I don't know.
I have to think about it.
Dunkerslam only took like a year to finally manage a month without dying.
Damn.
That's a lot.
He's also like a main, like, uh, Neuter is his main game, right?
It's like what he does.
He's the Neuter man.
Shadow Fantasy 58.
Electricity?
That's where my worst enemy when I first started this game.
Arcs of electricity climbing up metal, getting shocked in the water or blowing up things right next to me.
Dude, I feel you so much.
I'm getting PTSD just reading that.
Shitty Ukuskivi ended my insane run the other day.
I was like blazing through the levels.
I went all the way down and I went all the way up and I was just blazing through all the old levels, looking for stuff.
And out of nowhere, poof, I got stunned in some water with an Ukuskivi and I couldn't get out and I died.
That was that.
Felt real bad, man.
But I also really learned to respect the Ukuskivi.
Yes, it is stupid.
Oh, okay.
I'm gonna... I need to brainstorm ideas how to deal with that guy.
By the way, I see people in the community or in the chat here also call that guy Steve.
Why is that?
Is there some kind of joke there?
Can you guys explain that?
I kind of want to know.
Heard some of you call him Steve.
Why is he called Steve?
Oh, you read his name.
Oh, you're right, Stivati.
Wait, is that the Finnish name for Steve?
No way.
Hold on.
That's gotta be another name.
Uh, wait a minute.
Oh, okay.
I just google translated Stivati.
It means steward.
He's the steward of the holy mountain.
Dude, that's a good name, steward.
Maybe I'll call him steward from now on.
As you know, the guy whose wife I definitely did not have relations with in a certain other game.
Stivati is cop.
Steward.
Yeah, he doesn't sound like a god anymore.
He sounds like someone who does the god's dirty job, right?
Like a steward.
Someone who watches over that place.
It's his job to protect it or whatever.
Yeah.
It sure is, Lilith.
Also 69 viewers.
Nice.
Mall cops, specifically.
That's amazing.
I'm imagining the guy from, uh, what's it called?
Blort.
Something, Mall Cop.
It's a movie.
If that is him, you know.
Paul Blort, I think.
Exactly.
Paul Blort.
Yep.
Paul Blort, Mall Cop.
A lot of the enemies are named quite plainly if you speak Finnish.
It doesn't surprise me.
Makes a lot of sense.
But some of the names are still insane.
So, like, the Finnish way of writing names is just such long words, you know?
It's crazy.
Okay, I need to eat some food now.
I gotta go.
And I'm gonna put out the next Prey episode now, so enjoy that one for those that are following that.
Guys, thanks for watching and watching me struggle in this game.
It's been a real struggle lately, but I'm still having fun, so that's all that matters.
Thank you so much.
I'll send you off to another streamer of Noiter.
Let's see who's streaming.